{
  "LANGHINDI": 34,
  "qu1": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>Which of the following is a unit of fractional surface renewal rate?</p>",
      "OPT1": "cm/sec",
      "OPT2": "cm<sup>2</sup>/sec",
      "OPT3": "hour",
      "OPT4": "hour<sup>\u20131</sup>",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Wkw/v0ACIC+JhZVbmq0HcA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Wkw/v0ACIC+JhZVbmq0HcA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.33",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu2": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>Assume that toluene is insoluble in water. The normal boiling points of toluene and water are\u00a0110.6\u00b0C and 100\u00b0C respectively. At a pressure of 1 atm, the boiling point of a mixture of toluene and water is</p>",
      "OPT1": "110.6\u00b0C",
      "OPT2": "100\u00b0C",
      "OPT3": "Less than 100\u00b0C",
      "OPT4": "Greater than 110.6\u00b0C",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "9m/iwvJKC6coEJr5HJJczQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "9m/iwvJKC6coEJr5HJJczQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.33",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu3": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>The surface renewal theory was developed by</p>",
      "OPT1": "Higbie",
      "OPT2": "Maxwell",
      "OPT3": "Stoke",
      "OPT4": "Danckwart",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Wkw/v0ACIC+JhZVbmq0HcA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Wkw/v0ACIC+JhZVbmq0HcA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.33",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu4": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>Kremser-Brown-Souders equation is used to calculate:</p>",
      "OPT1": "Height of a transfer unit",
      "OPT2": "Number of a transfer unit",
      "OPT3": "Plate spacing in plate column",
      "OPT4": "Number of ideal plates in a plate column",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Wkw/v0ACIC+JhZVbmq0HcA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Wkw/v0ACIC+JhZVbmq0HcA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.33",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu5": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>When the feed to a distillation column is saturated vapor the slope of feed line is</p>",
      "OPT1": "Zero",
      "OPT2": "\u20131",
      "OPT3": "\u221e",
      "OPT4": "0.5",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Dsdj/LJX8pBs6q+b96fwiQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Dsdj/LJX8pBs6q+b96fwiQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.33",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu6": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>Mass transfer coefficient (<em>k<sub>c</sub></em>) according to the boundary layer theory varies with mass diffusivity\u00a0(<em>D</em>) as</p>",
      "OPT1": "<em>D</em><sup>0.5</sup>",
      "OPT2": "<em>D</em>",
      "OPT3": "<em>D</em><sup>0.67</sup>",
      "OPT4": "<em>D</em><sup>1.5</sup>",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "9m/iwvJKC6coEJr5HJJczQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "9m/iwvJKC6coEJr5HJJczQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.33",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu7": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>If a temperature gradient is applied to a homogeneous solution, a concentration gradient is usually\u00a0established. This phenomenon is called</p>",
      "OPT1": "Dufour effect",
      "OPT2": "Soret effect",
      "OPT3": "Knudsen effect",
      "OPT4": "Seebeck effect",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "fhPK/WKkcuYMengj9uY6cg==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "fhPK/WKkcuYMengj9uY6cg==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.33",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu8": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>In the absorption of solute gas from a mixture containing inert in a solvent, it has both found the overall gas transfer coefficient is nearly equal to the individual gas film transfer coefficient. It\u00a0may therefore be concluded that</p>",
      "OPT1": "The process is liquid film controlled.",
      "OPT2": "The gas is sparingly soluble in the solvent.",
      "OPT3": "The transfer rate can be increased substantially by reducing the thickness of the liquid film.",
      "OPT4": "The transfer rate can be increased substantially by reducing the thickness of the gas film.",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Wkw/v0ACIC+JhZVbmq0HcA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Wkw/v0ACIC+JhZVbmq0HcA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.33",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu9": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>The relative volatility of a binary mixture at the azeotropic composition is ________.</p>",
      "OPT1": "1",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "M3GN47IE5BMfhyY9KAJXiA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "5kxMa8YwwyHwJY15nzG3sQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "2",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "Alphanumeric",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu10": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>The concentration and hydrodynamic boundary layers over a flat plate are of equal thickness if\u00a0Schmidt number will be equal to ________.</p>",
      "OPT1": "1",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "M3GN47IE5BMfhyY9KAJXiA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "5kxMa8YwwyHwJY15nzG3sQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "2",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "Alphanumeric",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu11": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>For steady state diffusion of \u2018A\u2019 through non diffusing \u2018B\u2019, the ratio\u00a0<img align=\"absmiddle\" alt=\"\" src=\"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAAEkAAAA3CAYAAABAW2dtAAAF/UlEQVRoQ+2abUhbZxTH/5Yx9kE6KTKMdWzMom5fRhOVjTLqCyuUmlkTpsxZUyJOUEedi6+Lo512JTO0iC9MxawVN9aWZBNrOywa86EwrTqGhRm7ysqmjnUUKbJXyXafe6PJvYnJk5h749jNx3Duvef53XPOPc/5PzH/MD/Iv4AEYmRIwSNEhhScEWRI0YW0jlmzGul1k6wbCr0Vt/s12L9n06sNrNqqkajt3XIzuX0GCwYVHqNwXEoT0SPJtXoTxmIdzk0q0T4zBIMqjr++VRt0iR8iYfwrmHLipVw79bNEhwTXAiyvvQ/Hk99hcEWPmZFTUMVuhRM2Zs1IUz9E30IbcvZ6/qdegQSG4kMikXJyDU0dwKnnLyDJeg39mmfA4XCnXG8mnDf0SNmdjMQv3CRSDl5R4pZJibvmEqSffxbW2+eh2f84A4mrW+oHLVgw5WCvBFERziNEjiQSKTU4uVaNG/o07FmfhlldjNFjn2HEkIlY/AibrgDD+V/gkubpbfz/C8u2WmT0KjEZpWgTGRKJFD2uKHvcRdm9YO0PqCVF/MV7MKcZgMsjTEGP9QvJtWxDpb4T8/MvozVKdUtcSKRoH20FOgegT3mCg+C6D1t5HrQ/vQOnJQ5nM2ag23bxv2Ki4V3MFRQDJQPYd33Qc59w8ibMa8SF9GgCDYfmUPiNASqv5se1aMHR1AuILz0A+8/qbdLIhfXZLlTZX0K3QYExXSmmdFej0iaICMmFRxNGpJkO+IGwxqQhU8TrRqGoH/dftEn9qvoa2d3VTMvwG2OvRfO+Dq62hRkR4V4mEiR+tw1kMY0kv+6QWlOeoYWj1l+X/QcWLaVILbvKX1epFSuXNFCEu9owrxMJUpjeuC9jizVTylp6PNsYtuksYmr8Aj91d/Ykuqt3HyS2sDdjqbKbv4Vhty9jyF/pgkYh7e5ul0HiWoTDUxrMCZvLjVmmXajAgz7p93i7CJJgKpDcjpnN1GKjSItBNjuSUWq1B2g+6VIoFKtdBCkUt6W1lSFR8GYhxcTEUJj+P0z86SJyJFG8exmSDImCAIWJHEkyJAoCFCa8SGL3R+l1uEcuVFR5jVndd+I1daSv82r4KB4WCZNo+Oibbq5lTBj1yD03j6z2L91jVu/lkZFrNqoT+qI3l5bYRz81iYwpqnDG8RD2wb+5Mau3VibaHorblryyVE4hUErrox9IJFKMWGuqYTSgYzAmdfGVVzblPsdhZ6RHqaFAktZHX0gkUg5aobz1ATLvdkKdbsFzXlqZeGJiCJAk9tEXkltMfI+Vb9xj1tFct/Lq4vT74SMiTAhDgCSxjz6QPGIiJxZyY9ZqLNWSIv4CnIyYWARz4LrBDs606D00FHgmLfxa+nz+fMe+xCRkH9k6mo469rPt9ctqgrW3EZqUwLKoABIpiGV4Gy1ei9vUyn5Bm7MNcWcrgqgWxL4J+k4H5jM/CuELSBtJ4fooUIvX78BS9QaMCR1BfRRAIjpXJeYKLXyxkNXPcmCMfxXZ9t+ROxmgaBMZ6fVvUdDwJ0pMT+E6tepKCylcH4VqMYFGp8DwIZEFpn2MVB8IRAPrYIp4LSYVTRjfVkwkNew07NmnYUicgE4VSHgU5hYlpHB9ZFNuUy12YfHmRQzYk1DWfBwpXqdc/DW8W5B4nSzbTAuknk3l1aHzjFV5d/QWExmdn3XKFILqGhzSjnzk1T8FsurPoKYwD2qVIqiOF7kNrjsly8ZWvdBJP4/ebuvDqsZZ36OBzQLmhUz3o/H4J0gYCi4sRAgSKdYtaEUlerbOHnGFMuiXMBIbuqD38Kcm05xo4W4cEUhsm6C/j0qr9yk2t/ohSk8VlIrAwM85KDbyy+BsGA56vmDnkNha9Ram3vzU52HidechQmKB5OFy0TWutXGtYrqjEcV38uHgHXb1f98dQuImAtpBrkvzFHvhydoKWKOgvHJLFp5LIP8dQf3FVtScyISC4vTFDiGF+Eb/o+YyJIoXJ0OSIVEQoDCRI0mGREGAwkSOJBkSBQEKEzmSZEgUBChM5EiSIVEQoDD5F88CGJj4Qn7pAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC\" />\u00a0is ________.</p>",
      "OPT1": "1",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "M3GN47IE5BMfhyY9KAJXiA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "5kxMa8YwwyHwJY15nzG3sQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "2",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "Alphanumeric",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu12": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>The flooding velocity in a plate column, operating at 1 atm pressure, is 3 m/s. If the column is\u00a0operated at 2 atm pressure, under otherwise identically conditions, the flooding velocity is ________. (Rounded off 2 decimal place)</p>",
      "OPT1": "2.12",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "07jMdpYtPrDeanLM6roPTA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "5kxMa8YwwyHwJY15nzG3sQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "2",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "Alphanumeric",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu13": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>It takes 6 hours to dry a wet solid from 50% moisture content to the critical moisture content of 15%. The time it will be take to dry the solid to 10% moisture content under the same drying condition is ________ (in hrs). (Rounded off 2 decimal places)<br />\r\nThe equilibrium moisture content of the solid is 5%. All these percentage are on dry basis.</p>",
      "OPT1": "1.188",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "WFIsS699qduolnVkRlhNng==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "5kxMa8YwwyHwJY15nzG3sQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "2",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "Alphanumeric",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu14": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>The gas flow rate in an enriching section is 45 mol/h. The minimum reflux ratio is 0.98. If the internal reflux ratio is 1.2 times of the minimum reflux ratio, then the float rate of liquid entering in to the enriching section is ________ mol/h (Rounded off to the nearest integer value), if the gas\u00a0flow rate is changed to 28.5 mol/h.</p>",
      "OPT1": "34",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "M1sdaUs1Jb/nh2+zgGR/5g==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "5kxMa8YwwyHwJY15nzG3sQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "2",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "Alphanumeric",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu15": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>Choose the correct statements from the following:</p>",
      "OPT1": "The diffusion coefficient in a liquid is 10<sup>\u20134</sup> to 10<sup>\u20135</sup> times the diffusion coefficient in a gas",
      "OPT2": "The diffusion coefficient in a liquid is 10<sup>4</sup> \u2013 10<sup>5</sup> times the diffusion coefficient in a gas.",
      "OPT3": "The binary diffusivity in gases varies directly as pressure.",
      "OPT4": "The binary diffusivity in gases varies inversely as pressure.",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "MfW1aVa49JnBBbjbyREKzA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "MfW1aVa49JnBBbjbyREKzA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "5",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu16": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>Which of the following statements is/are false regarding transfer unit of a packed column?</p>",
      "OPT1": "Number of transfer unit depends on the type and size of packing.",
      "OPT2": "Height of transfer unit is unity if the average driving force available is equal to the concentration change.",
      "OPT3": "Height of transfer unit is the same as the height equivalent of a theoretical plate (HETP).",
      "OPT4": "The number of transfer unit is determined by the concentration change and driving force.",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "1tsLNxDzUM4tAESa/gW9mQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "1tsLNxDzUM4tAESa/gW9mQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "5",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu17": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>For a particular tray in a gas absorption column, the following data are available:<br />\r\nSuperficial gas flow rate (taken on basis of \u2018active tray area\u2019), <em>G</em>\u2032 = 198 kmol/m<sup>2</sup>h; overall gasphase volumetric mass transfer coefficient.<br />\r\nk<sub>c</sub>a\u2032 = 2.1 kmol/m<sup>2</sup>(s) (kmol/m<sup>3</sup>); depth of froth on the tray, <img align=\"absmiddle\" alt=\"\" src=\"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAAA8AAAAXCAYAAADUUxW8AAABbElEQVQ4T2P8DwQMZALGUc2khRy1AuwHw+0FKQyeDUdRrOeKmc9wpMWBgQ+LoxA2/7vJsKTlFoNTjS+DFBNQ5ZerDAs7jjHoViQzGPGABDABdmf/e8ZwoGUxw8eUQgZ/KTacAYFF8yeGmwsmM+zSy2bINRLAG4Jomn8xvDgwlWHGh2CGugA5BuyORZiHpPkfw5ebKxg6V4ozZNc4M0gQ0gk0A67534u9DK1TXjKEVUQwqIMD6BfDsw0zGfZppzJEfJ7OYBE0ieGDSz/DkTkBDBJQyyGa/z1i2JgdzlC8/QWqHwXzGFadLmQwYvnCcK4/mqFZsIthbYI63DtEJpI3DAdq0hn2usxkaHYQgVtAnGZgGlgY2MHA0DOdIV6Vg0TNLzYwpHneZ8gAewFraOOO0j/n+hkspikybEEKLJBqIpwNSfORdwwYIoTNGNIK7eDpnAjNoJAOY0i46skwoTyewUkVkUWI0IzbOxRpBgCsGMG8imWKHQAAAABJRU5ErkJggg==\" /> = 0.25 m; Total pressure <em>P</em> = 1.2 bar;<br />\r\nTemperature = 35\u00b0C. Calculate the point efficiency?</p>",
      "OPT1": "0.26",
      "OPT2": "0.36",
      "OPT3": "0.46",
      "OPT4": "0.56",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "fhPK/WKkcuYMengj9uY6cg==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "fhPK/WKkcuYMengj9uY6cg==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.66",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu18": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>A tube of a gel solution of 1.05 wt% agar in water at 278 K is 0.04 m long and connects two agitated solution of bromide in water. The bromide concentration in the first solution is 0.2 gmol/litre of solution and is 0 in other. What will be the molar flux kmol/(m<sup>2</sup>-s) of bromide at steady<br />\r\nstate? Diffusivity coefficient at 278 K is 0.727 \u00d7 10<sup>\u20139</sup> m<sup>2</sup>/s.</p>",
      "OPT1": "3.6 \u00d7 10<sup>\u201310</sup>",
      "OPT2": "3.6 \u00d7 10<sup>\u20139</sup>",
      "OPT3": "4.80 \u00d7 10<sup>\u20139</sup>",
      "OPT4": "8.40 \u00d7 10<sup>\u201310</sup>",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "fhPK/WKkcuYMengj9uY6cg==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "fhPK/WKkcuYMengj9uY6cg==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.66",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu19": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>In a distillation column, the feed is saturated liquid with 80% more volatile component of A. The\u00a0distillate is with 90 mole% A. What is the minimum reflux ratio with relative volatility 2?</p>",
      "OPT1": "<img alt=\"\" src=\"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAACsAAAAtCAYAAAA3BJLdAAACXklEQVRYR+2YT0iTYRzHPwuPzkO3eemweO3gbSZFELRh5CGM7VSHGY5glHia/UGhyyLqHZGkkEiLTUgQHOIEpXBB4CX2QrCgbdTFyAl1CT1EjLc2XWu61V5Hz2vK8x7f9/f83u/zeb7P73l/r+VH4WKfXBYpVtBKHTCyG1kSi3NEBt7To43itjUJ4lY/7R/IfienPWdh+hHDa+1cXJniQeYyS+kgzpZD9bMKiviL2Je8s57EqXwl1nsGz7KfZDqAY+/AYsCzH6XYRpwiyTZCzcgYSdYIpUZi6pPV04S7nfhS/22dLc67VLKiH7ZDsKt7Vm/rk21kvQSNkWIFgTVy3Ip69e7zShvsnpmxEZtkLRaLseg6UaJ7T2mDf7JMNZJIsiaR1dnIvmJx7ikDqR60iBtb+c3FZy94fCfAYPRt4W47XjXEkL8LpdmcJnLLBnoOLT7P9MNx1jpPsHJ/jMz1JdL3nLSUxOqfYlw5fpt8cIqxPoX1xF0uucZBnSUe6KRZFM6KvBViM1hdp1HWZ+lt9bCsJkkHHGw1s9/Ihr20DR+taMe/kLhxDtfkWdNa9OoNlotVi/31TUuQzEIfyuaqlybg+4yajBNwiGdrTGxeI3Ssg8FTM6yWfZwnF+un1ZORYmttgQNM1v6khmcPM7Nqzg87Y2SptfNL995crZiA2PpVJVbPhulu85HaVmcLB4I2wvkOFW5FeBZ0Yc1Ocs0Zoml0ngn3Ecw4Fn6LLZWs6A449nK9LfwGfT3BzQv9RHOFIJsXNTKEv0sx5UAoypIfMqKcK8lKsnKDifLAfiP7E13U3olsxufPAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC\" />",
      "OPT2": "<img alt=\"\" src=\"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABwAAAAqCAYAAACgLjskAAACJklEQVRYR+2WP2gTYRjGf2fVKZYODgaHDkK9IVukIB1aTxCKhEIEQU1qSRAFrRFJ0yVZtKJNjvi3UJCG2hYKDhl0aIl44pClNCBY8AwVRakNFETLISLl9Ku0g+KZ5NKUYPNuB+99D8/vfb6PV/ohik0sqfYEjTza9CMeXJynK3cPr3N7RTwsHH5nMZdh6uFdogUXJ95Pknzdw1N9AKVxW7UEn/Fq10GUli+kTx/iWPYcs3oYd2UGKWGGH+qCZc20jlTg2uzQmDqpToXgy6rew9UcrDkbe/N7KPYlKrqPJYSmrBAWba4LFkVUbsMWRSpJUkmk7GwnWxRpSTxtNtUSUhMj/4Tha2H6xuaEHxfdyWFuhNpwVrBHWTtc1uiXQxT61kS+zpE630u2a5T73mbsaloKruRU5APzxD+u76Imy1oU2QcTFayLloJmPkXn/pvsGZlkKODCwTfyqSBnP4V4HG4V3/bKGqm5gBYNcPh6Bmd3gjvtDbxraOOUv7VKMxQGzMUst6PjFJreEk9moCPCqHoJv9u58TM0F9Kcadc4+jyJd+9OIT7D+K0YPfEdJGYnCLubbDG1QGqQUz14lmLogwqN60f/Sq6PFwMaUwHZlksLwc9C0CcEL/9FMCJiOs2gsnsjHYqzjBlUzxWWelViXhmHoZO+GuJC4STakB/ZYe8m/uNp+/OlOUJkpJ/g8Q5abIqtIqmlt9TWiIr+VHdYFFG5Df8/0p9rGHqSTKot+AAAAABJRU5ErkJggg==\" />",
      "OPT3": "<img alt=\"\" src=\"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAACgAAAA8CAYAAAAUufjgAAABUklEQVRoQ+2XP08CQRTEZxNa7aUl0Q9AYqwspKIikQ9gQU9l/A5oY0NhA9HSwhC1oLExsYOKBihtoJf6VMDwT723MJfLJcy2b2d38nvvNjfu83shwcvJINkdESQBQgRFcE4gwKj/iuZjHeVOAe3bU+yxeDz09gwGA7SfnnF/fYPh4RHeL6voXbygWznBrscF7BZPgz3s5I6x/9HAWbqIt6sWuudZpNjbPfS2wcVDBg8yuApVBD3GLHSLCMZKMOjXkD8ooZOod3CM4Od5uVvBkYnhPVxvBtl+baCXwQ2gLUlEMHKCzjn2TEQZtdVith0iuM0ErRRn1Vl2U/3vGbRSnFWPxtfslH8MhqS4icH4Ul74V2ylOKseAU0ZZCGK4HYTtFKcVWfp/f1Q+6S4GFOe/mbYNougCLIEWL1mUARZAqxeMyiCLAFWrxkUQZYAq0/8DH4BGj3oXHr7C5wAAAAASUVORK5CYII=\" />",
      "OPT4": "<img alt=\"\" src=\"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAACoAAAA/CAYAAACW2FpzAAACiklEQVRoQ+2YT2gTQRTGv4jHtoi3COIhEHPoLSpKQTEhhx6kkpwEaUqCmFMqkljBniRFTIq21EpLZSU5KBQSpIm0KN2KkIt0QYjgJtRLJUkPHvyTgxSzMf9Kk3R1d2G6beDNcWfmzTe/+ebtvjVUqg1d0AwklPEpEVHGQEFEiagsgVIO/MoSov4NDAlP4DQeZQ1KdTwZj26jKLzB8uIMxrf6cW3zJR5lR7AqhmDrO6I6MOuB/xC6hs+9F2Az/0DCfRmutA/rYgDWgwOqdOu/klCt1lDIo0RUK1DyqGZiShP+71FJBDdogzdzKPNobW/NSxT70r5RU+TA8il9PSl5Tms/EdVKTGl89xCt7oRJXb/fvwe6hyj9gFC6HRr76eg1AlMc3kJUQin3HitLz+HPDEGIOmHcmV6tRt/OTcAdjKFYe2YcRiR6Dz6HGT2KS7AZYKiUCxUhmcLi1Dy2zp3HZngW2TurEB/a0Fdf4zdynBc3N0bwIuSois+DH/fA/qAATzyFBecp6FGbNoVm0Wu/CPOvV3CfcCEdWYcYsKJRdH4DPxbB91sTu3X9Tx5jFjvCjjgKreTZwJON0n6ZigkZoTLz/giYtJxBcOCwC60TvY6PIR7LHotOR9/67lNFdBv5xG2cnTEhmRyFtUcPh6KjuFMhVMoncOPSawykHsNjaVw3PZo2j5Y+YNLF4fh0WFeRNRDqhZY+gRt9BgTv6y5yj1Apx2HwtBeZtjwKSMU0pu8+Rdk/i4D1mB4nvWeNBtGmN2Md3aZaPvWVMXXlKoLv6u+kzhEYjq8h6jy57+Lpo4Q1YiJKRFkTYB2PPEpEWRNgHY88SkRZE2AdjzxKRFkTYB2PPEpEWRNgHe8voXfsU59aNrwAAAAASUVORK5CYII=\" />",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "fhPK/WKkcuYMengj9uY6cg==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "fhPK/WKkcuYMengj9uY6cg==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.66",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu20": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>A solid is to be dried in the falling rate period from the critical moisture content <em>X<sub>C</sub></em> to one tenth of it\u00a0<img align=\"absmiddle\" alt=\"\" src=\"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAADQAAAA9CAYAAADid0ojAAAF1UlEQVRoQ+1abUxbVRh+WIjxx4bEj0xYjLhhwQTjsmIj8SNbESZxbFqSyRgfTRsCMgZoWnDSMXRsC0LYQIYjSwlFQYNSdZUwWCj8kEQnnV9LgAYW1LAu0RhEYpaFVO9pb7/gwj23vQVkvT/bc8/7Pu/znuc95z037F/mwQZ6wkKA1jmbIYbWOUG4mxiag9XYjt7IDJTKt2HTqlEzh3GDHgNPZKJYFiXYLjdD8+Mwnu7CbK4GqviIVYPiMXQHNnMTzk2/hOOqBGwW4MFSQPYZmKtbMZ21VmBc3vsHahGgO5gxHsdJFKFF8Sg33QsW1McnQjvlCduOulGMa57C78ZiRGe0uv9w/i5FuIAI+w6dhaW+GkN7qqGRRlLN4gPIPmNEfsEsKi6pIFlx0ZDonUFWsgmywcuolT/IGrNj3tKI9PTryDGfFSVd6X1yuuAF6DasbUdQG1mFi8ux4xMjEr1sJPYmY9RUCunmTbDbrkCn7EFs43uigHGa+wPmCiX697Z7BW55sjyA7ONoS2tGZPs5KKIok2T+KurTizB2tAetSVZUiQ6GOG7HnFmHXf0v4lqtHHwS5QFkMyJPOYvKPr50844Om2KaKci2hyNO+66IzHjZmTOj4tlrOPi9BlKeWLOAhEXBh3AHS1nofbkLJo1sGYll1pzlK3Q2nYC24zr7eirK9RVQH9wNCZOuKz4CsocFtACbsQzK2WL0qeLpixmReN1J9D8Wg1snvsaTpo+WqpFjzBsw3J+JksP7II26h/GdKdrmz6CvncbeT6shj+Ar27/BmPc6bpR8wsy/clViAc0zCzwTTds/gEHxCJU8gnW0M7GOEZGtmGzLRdyHSW6BcE5ChEaNgj9LOdhjnHx7GAk1OTyKSuYh/qnQvauFVxi8ANG94PDTFfXYKpx3VXKu1CO5H38BccMdUEnupQsU5yj6gLOA6Cl1glEh2fIaJnwEhLDBsKT+B3WjJPUiHOoUXxuLYUFCw4WIzF2AU5E1vBkkDBBRwugMdLhtFqDnZjMj8zYmx/cgo8Nr+5DbjR8ODGLnl6m4aVAgKgB+ALLGi/H8jXzenYcwQIKccjoR3SpbxKSgSdjBggF9i/LY/Rir/gmm7K3+WOR8x25tQ1qcESmOFKTbi3Ebv40fy6V4euwY5kzZWGk1sgwFBxDAbo8aHkCdoRKFKRK2ThHZHsLYfTKkS2nOPOsGEFFEGyxfdKKpWIsOGxv/3eXQH03Dc6kv8BdVVv7XCUNiZe96YkgUTIIB8dehsLAwUVzjm4S7kStY5fgB8TkS3P9DgP6nDNknYHhVwfRAtOj7XInHmU17kOuQWIm4jChsOEAc8RKHoXkrzJcvwVAyiQMWsln1Oicz/125cAp52g6QuhqV2wBDpRopEr7ugLe3gmXbn60POVYPoK/7fehuJeDQrx+jYUKJwfEazwnU/guM+ftQvKCB+TxzkPt7ELqsPJxhct7VKaJLylUDxOzHtiRBLvnLeXwYKcTouKeR4dyctmCnu3fn7F3EJw8gx6efxwdrVQB5O0FUcjEg14EP0E94TqxOkGpMCeqqrgtA5NicjkRtHHsIZNcVe0gcCS6gQOsQF0PiAhJ4BKfvqnBne7ABCW6S0L8gHNBDHGvoNB7uGeJteHhs0Qc8sEaj2yIXQ1yK5vptEjVeQsGncQD9kgi8FUy8cbRq5VD/vKgOOXp1rzBVpwCDXccg32JF25FD0IW/g+8uKrCNr2HqQiq8Fcy86VeznmXGu31FnNhR565HdtsIGt8qxJuOnnYCcuvqUVmYQnn0ZhEJb9azUd7fhZguml4zf5KIN0LYRcKiC68y6GNqePvH4jlLM5O/F16EJOorSRpHxBkj1Cfhl8bi+Ek5S4CXxg4rZIdcdBazZUG6jaOEAohyrc9a21AfXri134arzZ345pnDfn2iQk3EkoGBfZJzN3285H+M1/LNEENrGX0a2yGGaKK0lmNCDK1l9GlshxiiidJajtlwDP0HxbZ7hqTB4ocAAAAASUVORK5CYII=\" />\u00a0The equilibrium moisture is negligible. If the falling rate is linear in <em>X</em>, the drying\u00a0time is <em>t</em><sub>1</sub>; if the drying rate varies as <em>X</em><sup>2</sup>, the drying time is <em>t</em><sub>2</sub>. Then\u00a0<img align=\"absmiddle\" alt=\"\" src=\"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABYAAAAxCAYAAADeHVm1AAAC2UlEQVRYR+2WXUhTYRjHf4uILsKrpFZUF8bchSE0qYtdpFNRLwY1iYJshmB2EUSy+YVC4Ef4EZtiYAmCzgKL7UIzg+XUIILh6kZirqsIPUQRZV5EyKl5Nm3qPs5xehHsvT7v7/zf//u8z/NX/QkudmGpUuA1V1NWrNdXyorEVoiCF4e9m/dF3bQbDip+mzE8FlnyNKItg2F/C4a0PTsF/kVgwEzmzGUWB02oFWNhq+LlAO6+VsqtQwgSUEfN5AvFdkS3QvQzUHKRmarnDJqOresVBR9jE0+wz5zlcYKTRAcveajV9pE5PUSFZj+i8JruuluMHr7AGe99Oo73JrQoKnjF14XW+I2H4YsThXe8+plBruYHrvI8SunYDjjexX1KBvwVT20x19PvMpo9x72pbGxtBtIkp5MChze79XT2XCJPX4BOvS98gUmB4xVtCFxzagS/RcfeOJ8q625SGRpoKxzbYbBUhvk4rk7ib1/zPbpsmYqX8XUZybFOR1AyMDunNjygyF/IBCtvFutglUqlfPemHZHZZ/cVJy13EyClOPEwTdbzGB7/RvCNYG/4QNHTOzs5TEOtsyzY0BM93VgnUzTzlNizCSyyHHDT12rBOjQX4qjrmdxGtoiqWAwMUJLppWqxF5M62HVFAZ/DjuVaB1Ibyq3H+aAOkyY0V6KtKOBwCmo/yfREBZpgCFrx2TjvzKK/pZBDn1cn9g2q3ca4J4kCDrVI45em8MWtILjsTGTdlKJAUH4ofuW/oXp2DIvugEzFMcJK5G4pHuR4aZgP5Q55VkhTopn04S6y3zqYOt1I24a0GY4HI8XMh62SBxZclB8pxW3upMeUh96oQx0RNsUFF5XnxtE/s1GhVXR5capV/Iir0srsFRsthqPEC7fy26a4gKexmZcFTQmhq9LkgSXobR7ldNJvOhFX6dp5ZYC/B8uvLDihx7d6ZHbGDIcywEo6xL9v/z/wX20x2H08albnAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC\" />\u00a0is</p>",
      "OPT1": "1",
      "OPT2": "0.521",
      "OPT3": "0.256",
      "OPT4": "None of these",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "9m/iwvJKC6coEJr5HJJczQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "9m/iwvJKC6coEJr5HJJczQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.66",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu21": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>In a process benzene is evaporating in to a dry nitrogen, at 297 K and 101.3 kPa, the resulting mixture has R.H. = 50%, it is required to recover 50% of the benzene by cooling to 283 K and\u00a0compressing to a suitable pressure.</p>\r\n\r\n<div>\u00a0</div>\r\n\r\n<div><img alt=\"\" src=\"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAAaEAAAAyCAYAAAD1LWSbAAAVM0lEQVR4Xu1deVxU19l+1HxZNSGLEbXRxlTR72fairiVfBVREv1QQSZqjAoEpJCIbFHcIC6QIEvYxERFkEVtMIWwqLggkvxiNQq2RhtBrTab4E/rR5TaxNrpd+42c+fODDLOwjC89z+Gc88597nvuc9519PjP+wCXYQAIUAIEAKEQCcg0INIqBNQpyEJAUKAECAEeASIhEgQCAFCgBAgBDoNASKhToOeBiYECAFCgBAgEiIZIAQIAUKAEOg0BIiEOg16GpgQIAQIAUKASIhkgBAgBAgBQqDTECAS6jToaWBCgBAgBAgBIiGSAUKAECAECIFOQ4BIqNOgp4EJAUKAECAEiIRsIAM9evQAFaawAdA0hEkIkFyaBBc1thICREJWAlbeLS12G4BMQ5iMAMmlyZDRDVZAgEjICqAqu6TFbgOQaQiTESC5NBkyusEKCBAJWQrUtkaUJaxExbhsFPo9p9MrLXZLgUz9mI7ATZwv24DQCjfsKvRDf1kHJJemo0l3WB4BIiFLYdpchoABsUDpESIhS2FK/VgAgW9RFjAJKqTgCpGQBfCkLiyNAJGQpRDlSeg9OB/ej2TPZ0gTshSu1I+ZCAgkFO68FY3JnnicNCEz8aTbLY0AkZAhRHnTWiRUKQfZf0fCPzUNq8O8MKz3XTQ3lCBz6XKk1DUD/f2RXr4Bkf/9A8o17bkOQ1F6JQd+/R/geyezh6XFtrv2J5rWVEmoYxD0909H4epgeA172LBcjn0MFzlTnNgeeAH+Mk2d5LK7ypF9PTeRkN77+BHn8/3hcfQ1nMz1w8DbZ5G/eDucNiTDD5UIznRCBrejbON+n4fglmg0VQdh2FVOE9qIF+ursHR0b9KEOizn7MNaW4PPD+zFjTlZeth1uJtu0FB9Ph/TPE4h9GQ6/Ab+iMb8VUh1Wo68CSeNy2VPQROKfbEEjUtHQ9gWCReRUDtC03YetQc/xYH8Nswpj8ZoOXDdQNZs+YhEQnpoq9HWkIUZM/4M72wfDOnZC04jJ8FzGGfI4D6YR3D2xgVURCxDEVOG8EIq6huXYvS17kZCDKfzn2F/5XZEnPFBg9zfcLcBacPdsOyvCnAlrKQFrdPOA6kGCBwQfRpFys64vpmWmr4ZGyLd0b+nLZdNJ43VdgJpM97CGe8Y+Ax5GEww8bLnMPRuTy4f6G4kxK3RalQWZuOMz0cK/yz736E8vBsQI6xdZslILVyNMC8OQ+11tyENw92WgZc4pcxKzXjzuwpFhkRBspCM7Y/uIJbmroZ2SUjdcgr7/vgpKuOyUXtbPtQvMW9tANye/jnGebvC2SGRFj6yB89ewBcbC4D43YhoTcIY1QUszFuCOdN+A+xUwW2zd/ciIXUzGqr2YHfmFrSMHY9vUjahKfawrr+BI5dRpXA9mgjPx+8lHG1oSJsBtuaNkBAnd2rcrI3D8MlJeDS1XrOjVzcfRdaKSFQ6RyItai5G93/Q3PXQNe7nd+lf4m9f5CIOkagZtw9TjMllNyEhdXMDqqp3IzPuO4yddx0p6X9HrI5/9g6+L4vBmPB/IrE2A0HDbqE2LgiTk/6Lyd0OpoE76b57aYMEcZNpUBO6jtrlUzE5pY9Mdu+g+UQuVvhWwjkpAVELx3aPDZIZK8cICd1BS10qggP3YGBkDF6f/go8hkouTfa/U7U49mkp1tS5o/STQAzteRct5TF4Keoiwst2I8pV1xxlxvw64VbOHLcGlb9aKQgmb3YLRMnED5FwIxbj0ifgcGMiPP5xjH0AwxBzNEBGQuFoyatFddBwnR2QQ5k9eBJqQp/Jv8WwW+X8bvCojBj4F8Yt4PFHMOk40xDvacboCAlxXXK703S8oMDX2O+dIDhWH1J9vhAhlSOQtXQsr/005kfDs2QEEiftRXC2EbkUSUjVskowG8v2BI4klzwJneuDyZ5DcKssHANUTbqbGnUj8qd5Iu7XO7Qbppu1WD58MooXKjZRkgxz2ny7JCTJbl/kNRUxYmPaKX8Z+93qItIlBzBAQkwDOLUJc/12YXBmCXJ8BxlWKVvK8VaOEzYkeuhE3Ng9Cpqd/BqkDMrBle0TcKV8J7LDmXnNJR31VW9iQNPH2uADvIzYAm5H44Y+54ux2DOQqfLcb0sxrvk9qFbWiSr77/BYEfsoBOcD/gWo3bQQw3sLK96RFrvO+xVNErYjoc1wV4TACyT0EVQGohLtXhZ1Jsh20A0HUb17I4JTnmeBLemYcGU/dmavwbKiwfxuPWbAeRRnxiOQD5jpD4/YZKYBzobLDyXtyGUMXC6Kcosg5HFawHBhQ+mYcsmChwyQEO9Pc4kDA0C7SRSJKfivMcJGUr5h6pAmJJGNi04gkoaExA3rva0BXUtSLT1bfRJSf4OKxXPx9pVQVPNajqWH7Mz+OLNOEqJPj4L3T6mIxWJseuhbtPz2NczvUw1vl2J4GfRLmDdnx1zsDJP2SGhUOq69zJlFuA8muzxiUZAWhYWjlXZypSb0KDODliMhNJxFIM7ULG6BbHRJSDDHhbG96lKR9NuYP+APyEuIE6IXNRuILmASYbvyVdHn4O19HQEs3SxlUz9canHF/PmPo9rbE+95VekFFpgnld2LhAzJj8bfeDSsAyQki0z0LxVzrgyRkGSO2wwk/h6bgkaKPrsuKpfmClkH7tcnoZt1iB//BqpDSnE82lUnmsZ4fzdxoe4A9u4oA97KRThyMd4vG63iDU6RrK8lQM4YFXL+j/vxSXhmVmKr77PMtLcPH32QjJyaFva7Mzxj0rE+fALzM3FmvxocKCvG0V8EwPvih3h7x5dCm8j1WBYyGUOZpqG+UACVVyqwtgylgS4ddASKzu5DU1HKRxo9CGGntB9zddTqDiDYgSZ2TULtOVgF9jDuq2mPhHxLMSR9BfyG9ZaRyksKswXXv5yEKhD22CdsV78LzonLETzHg4XFC7sg7UekBAFfhDI7fINAMnnadncbMjD79DSU8ubQVuZrWsB8Tf9ox9fUgZdn0ybSLv4ogkr3INdvMHryu/XpKJm7R8/Ma+7U7FcuJRy2GH9EYwEDMKwJmUdCopWj+BkkxgdjDh8MIpddpgmdm4UvPKcihdv7sA1Xnqxd15dLcyWt/fv1SYiZ2X43fjWudfij/h0qFs3E2zUcu7gj/tA2BAx9GOor5QifshpfhxSgJHqM8NLaTiJz9ga0Lt+IdzyeYX6k5ZgadQl+BR+yv51xu2kXYmYl4fuQeMz5SwoS+D6BR6csR35iENyevY66dW9iUWEr5hWUIoH1cV8kxKvaM3BolaSai47vBcAO5u+xtPpsv4vdTOEyRkJ63UqBBQV4Uc9nJpHQdfjHTsQ3J/oiftdKeCqCDAx/RJQDScEkV3CpIomZsc6yBrq5MWY+sZVvF7E4tFDrv+H9Fkw12qGfBG3uZBxTLi1MQrdfR+y8H3DioUjsSvRSBBkYM8c5mlyaK2n3RULROL5gOz7X8/e04VTGHMzJOif2Kmk0zmJgAvD+8XT4OHPG1R9xoWARpqX0xfs1yfAZ8ABu1q1jjtRRqNzkiwFoQuEsPyT0fRefb/Nl+g13iYR2LYKZAv3R77N1eCmwCuN5relnfIu7pzKYllUMV9lvJkPEfzwPwkeTUCpEuSxgpU2UWeUm923gBsdc7OxBO0xCxgMLtJrQt/DwcEJd3U/wz5PMGFow701CYvSTqgwuseuw5JWJ8HyiEm4KE54l3qf1+uA09Fmo8PlEDC2mzZHpWLdHQorAFskn5Mx8w4qSRnxwDReYcPs38Hj+MuouT9Pxpwnz6ggJOYJcmv4WTLnDgE9IJIcLr2Lb8TXwMBRiq1a2URsgITYN3rS3GGdjmanM/xFULV6DyyEZLHqORZ3dPYVMjXlOMeUnI7D7ZDR++aU+4ViChPgP2qqnsE+MFlJ/X4aQMR/BvU4e4WIKjPdgens+T8ji5jhG6Gmf4ImwYIwWTWnaEOuLSNQzd8rNcTsw/fQ7LLjjBLwURHTPKDjpg4JEjRZxb+Ky3Du2SE/8hy8ZT+0T5VD9NcpCVNjivsPipjhuvva7ObK8OY45g/Uj4fjfFuDPifoRrRoS4qLj6qfidCRLTD80VkFEHYiCcwS5tIhwG++kneg45lgLyEbemskG8oDkGos8RFuuCXGDtjLNidlQc0dia+FgfJj/FLI4LYgz80tExoIgjQVAGCIc80lIqIjgUjJV+FjxFRHW42JABhI9B3bQp2TaW7HfxW7acyhbC360YJzRyRPidn6xCKr3RgFvvuCivrhSRyXoFb/FAMbKwAS1EHrMEVFqCJyvDUZUsg/6igmEzMFj2EEvLfY7y1iEYyRG3RJD6Iv+qS1Vw0VGFmdiaYEz0lgbLUmah4Ol7tb1S95hOMQi8qJKxNFSo2j7cUy5FNd38CVFnpDkI/wXVh7OZ3LYh30HmJzFPYIc0S+sg7AyOu5HsULKIVekrhuMa0+HINnvyXvnuDmAXFpe8nR7NJInxAINyt9HVFQRvp0SgXULpsPLY6jojOMCBv6ATavfxe9bFvEai+sDoultLcvpFH1C0jCCz2YdzmCQxo8j/O8OC43mfELHMV4nGKEW9fg1/tf1WbQx851hc9w2PCf6rJjNz8TABCnBjHNsy+tvyUs7WhZ2h1vsRrSnFySCkEoa8T4ZLpQ4EfHBr4pVJ2TYGqisIPQxFJe4mmcb/43ANF88mr0Qc+QVEww6pRnZscjH1yevZXXVhEoKie7HMGmckPnO9fvVzNOY4ZKBn0lOf8u+ZjN70ybkcr5tY9n8Zg6ic7tjyaUx7UkWWMM2ISeyVsA3pghCwQSp9p7u2tepmMAjJvbh8h2rKbkUGzEXabN7IXvMfJ2KCRr510G5q8ulJSXOcF/tVExgTt4Ln+Pw0YPYunYn8+DIrhHzER/qhqcHjWdkcRdVmsAEro3kJxJ8OAALJohTYVHDq9j98WK4akw03P8Y2R0uROqSdLEiA1eJIRr+rz6Pr6JmicEOYjdTMpjvaDrAJ8VWCT+y3z5b3orFpkTH8TuTYDQtr9Crdm0tuB1rsVsLJWv3q6gJaHepB+L8msKs4pc0hC7JpbVlriP927tcduQZzGvT/WrH8XbgzXCxkv+HFrt5Ammtuzm/31vv3EJUljaJ2Fpj3V+/nIbug2SXPKv4f0gu7++tWPsu+5dLayPAfJP/YZf1h7GfEXhVe8YNbLVCKLaxp6Qdp/28f7udCW+aDMW1rZYPxSa5tNu3ThNjCHQzElIEJdjIJKMhIckxHpjCnwcDj5Uo3cIldHI2aS7HRaoU0Mzs1Tko3xCCsf2vCidj6lWRZr6W1HJUcXXE9Hw0svOMNP/rSvky3W9tWjNZ+t4kJAWPiOdkcUnApVmI9xsuZPsrKk/zZ2hxFaIV8qzrY1FWP5fLn+x/muoD3e+d0xMLCHQzEuqc1y6REJc57Vs6ErksaqzfVaHkTMyhGXxBVM+e9axM/3rc4CPIxMid4pGoqpqFryML4ZQRr02i5fxaMzfDaUsKX+1BuMSFLS9Uqf6eVQoORcK/g7Al3ldTfaBzUKBR7Q0BzeaI08J898A1lyUJ9/u76Lz/CxYe3of4J3Zihls+hvDBHE+KEWX9WFL3erjVr8fsmv/ho/f6sc1OCEu5yPeSStpwTysFC9yQVcoQHfUJP2GJZgNmb8jQfGyJAJGQDdAWFvu/WG5nJqpHhovVdqVoqGOIqS/CpCNvwu1MkDZpTmOe2YJxNV9hZOJCsQKyGAJ96XWU8tWUpUskIZZwyyfe8QQUjcJfvCPWr7LBg9IQXQoBDQk1V2BVtQsSpervYk5NacwxHBlSgEEqaAt0ahK90zCyejPOTosSTxA2dIy4RELS/Wo+gjGw8OcsVcNefXNd6hU6xGSJhGzwGo35hIRQ0BNYdW49nFJnQ3V3nZaEDJWe5+bKHWym2oUh+XItSKYJcSS0fRzOxSXggFuUaFKxwUPSEF0OAaO+Sk1Zqxp8/KsD8HFjtRlXFrKyNROhZtGpEyvGYI8OiTBTcmMxIlmzZTqBH3ISYlXBz2VgxYERWE1aeZeTFWtOmEjImuiKfRte7HL/VCAG/Imd5uq2HxP4RLq+uCrmvOgeGCdoQaGtYahUnFmkMcd944PUCQ+hl+8SwW5vg+ejIbomAsZISNc/1VNMNhb8Rf0Vx5RIpZuEE0ZZflZqGlaHeYmmX4mELiM2dRzQ6xVEdZdTcLumSHTKrImEbAC7ocXOlwqauBfue6TzXcRDyth5RM3c8cDbJ+K7N+JwVlZSRLinHvNPGSqyKprjLj4Hj8t1aPKSAhu6yWmjNniPjjaEQRLiSwUFosJ9o2DGbWtE2XtF+HqmCu5XT6E0k53D1WSojpp01EEBHtQUqZVIqJ7VBWxFXZM7NEENjgYmPc99I0AkdN/QdfxGvcXOL3RWXma+sVJBkr9IXmuNKzvyBjs5Z6UQEac3vOQT2oCm1T2Rx53HY/Bj0fF5U0vHRkCfhJQllwSZW/VUkjZ3SfQXpegEIIg4iRUwNodJpZVk5rimcHag3NtQpVwxWKDWsZGmp2sPASIhG8iHzmLnAwYSUDMl3nitOrFw5cYRH2gIhzeReJxCqKE6V/wzKAITNKVzBsjCbW3wsDREl0FAl4S4qLVUrKgZy05Llo4sUFb1Zo8m+SpHRiKi9RF4ZYVra/DpHTuhDEy4LdYFrGaVznMoYrPLSIp1J0okZF18+d61eUJCxNpO5ujlDywzNDZn/uDqU/WSnV/Ck9J0hD+T1U5JFwUJcX1ramUdggvvWFaeh2KDh6ch7BYBLQkJYdOBO19Efq4fBmoEUyz6uXcMDvNnPDE/JlfTT/UlvOu3Yebp1Xj3hyBs4Pw8rBrbiaw4xF97TVZwVUlC3BEv0smj4ShyWSv2SyZjuxUSG0yMSMgGIAtDSFV89+qPyCXsbZ/ACrruxAfs39Pmz8RUzemN0nkkf2Oh3DuwdDQ7BkN5tZesyiUb8h+OJNRRYqDN3nbXGYhFtjVwQTExQgK1zsWSnpsi0KcyGQHLpKKfqciJmA/f0f1wm0XELfYMRJFQDRSpORGY7ztaPPitvWRVeWK29gj3roMZzdSSCBAJWRJN6osQIAQIAULAJASIhEyCixoTAoQAIUAIWBIBIiFLokl9EQKEACFACJiEAJGQSXBRY0KAECAECAFLIkAkZEk0qS9CgBAgBAgBkxAgEjIJLmpMCBAChAAhYEkEiIQsiSb1RQgQAoQAIWASAkRCJsFFjQkBQoAQIAQsicD/A1RHMh921ck+AAAAAElFTkSuQmCC\" /></div>\r\n\r\n<div>What should be that pressure in kPa?</div>",
      "OPT1": "260.3",
      "OPT2": "270.3",
      "OPT3": "280.3",
      "OPT4": "360.3",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Dsdj/LJX8pBs6q+b96fwiQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Dsdj/LJX8pBs6q+b96fwiQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.66",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu22": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>A binary mixture consists of A (more volatile) and B obeys Rault\u2019s and Dalton\u2019s laws. The mole fractions of A in the equilibrium liquid and vapor phases, respectively, <em>x</em> and y. If <em>P<sub>A</sub></em> <sup>sat</sup> and <em>P<sub>B</sub></em> <sup>sat</sup><br />\r\nare the vapor pressure of A and B respectively, at the system temperature T, the system pressure <em>P</em> for <em>x</em> + <em>y</em> = 1 should be</p>",
      "OPT1": "<img alt=\"\" src=\"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAAIAAAAA6CAYAAAB4b1HYAAAH20lEQVR4Xu2be0xTdxTHv+iyLfER0szEapYlaoAZFpNRh+4hiNGMEcS1mThTCgF5RPCF5VEey5Yy5RXGc5O5MsDH4gwNSHwEtMAS5mRgTMQFcCMuRqtxIQzRGeO6/e6jtWX0we5t6aX3/sfl9nfP75zP/Z7zO/f+/P4hB8TDZz3gJwLgs7GnJy4C4NvxFwHw8fiLAIgAiEWgTzMg1gA+Hf5ZLQJNmBxphTbVgNCTlZBLX/D+UEwOQa/VoC20Gk3yV73fXhcsnEUFeAajPgPLFEDL3VphAGDUI35ZNjG4SwTABbicXMICkCHBpaEiRCyex31Id49AA3AISy9dQEnEK+6+m0fG50kBzHKegdJuIyBVoawpH2mbA7DQZMTAsUqoE0rRTaYkVdWitTgJqx+eI/LPXk9NVdWCu01ySD0ybXITWs73QVHaQf4IhqqsHPlpmxGwkIA5cAqV6hzLXCpai7Fv9Z9otVxPGZkqHOVy4FN+ADANoSFSid7UFhwlufHx0DGkly1CsW4roM9HpX8WeWIkxOfkfIQG94oMOJ+4CvepFJC9Cv1DaoR4tAR4gpEGFcJ7d+Dno3IsfzyIhvRv4V9cAjnOIKnSH1+URGDxJHX+YyTdO4Dh84kIuE8pQA3e6G+HOmShp1B1632cA0DLngLN05kRrkFLfS7kASYMlCsRfT0c1TErMA8SBG/ZQJ4mIuuTIzB0DGJstA17s5pB9AEry/oxpF6DB24B4Db08RuhaP5tGou3ILulCoXyAGCgCtHR1xBVHYMV8+bDP3gjIgIWk99MYMTQhcGxm2jbm4VmxmAG0ge+CADtxkkS4GjIOuOYJ4HE1WTsRVVuGjLNTwedwlnn3foRNQXzUXgjGePqrVCMfgDd/u2IjAROrJbhSJo7AWDi/mygHEGyPuQNNyMx4GXKYPRV5WJb5l8oMp8Dlbp+QMfgTVypaQQKv8fe8cNYq7iJON0ebI98mxisgOxIlK8D8AcMOe9DiVIMUdLIuJip4qki7hclbh28iDVVGaCUkZH6swi7uAdjWzegQnGJ/O5dPOo7itxtGejNtAJAMQadJSCO1I6533ujyUQ9QuA4Y5gwYShAkBI4bl1gWoq4NiTdqsaZNRoi5f7EYErqE3Aq7Ctox7IRWrGeLkzDH11mIO+NtwIgA/d0VAoLIkon/MN5CqDmSOf4j9CTes5q+TNOy76sU47hs5F4eOJ5oYfwbDSW70dcyAKSaw8gIqkBRurc4VAYlQpoiDrTaSDtJTRTOZbkF5XuO9QlBsN+Zp0JAEyOD+zZYVVYkqedkn3ZZcQNf4PIh23PCz2Q1NCoxf44GRaNUPAmEOmnzqkRajwEhaabTQMpWNDMzAeqRhjq4hBEpTkBH64BMGFATpAWS9rZ4sdS2d9AVP9x5ily+zETABjFSllSz6rFU7ay/wx9USfRrn7LAWhun4hX3cAlAEwjDYgM7EVsxzr0xKfQhZFUVYGm/CRspgsn6+Mp7ugzsbb+TXSz9QI/M54BAGbFii1CWE8BUZhBy9J0l+QMZLIs2JaIUiJatagv3MYUrj50uAAAm09LVrkUUNMdPXYn1uD69fXQcm3wOFqB0EEKR9l0SzJasY4gsJstAKcG9NkAyoNS8eBrqqFjXp7WYOnxudPgcZVhFwBg18zDaVYFoL3hKek9iKsf7gSUOkjO2QmAq9bZXOe6AtCKFf4rcuwBSIPVgRhzC5oGooRne//XJD3+IxcAmJpP7dlIFVm1SO9ahzq1FB3xKlyJP81jy9RVAFjFSpGg3U6DiV4ixgKnqP8/GUHnkUZ0rVAhTx7kc7WBcwBoOVXiGt29c7D0mexDefpP2FhHLQUfkxWCAnmSKh6XS64CwAC76dpuS8/CFlnzS6h69jSp9uk1/xaESF/0+BM42zd0CADTTLEumOz1v9llV9Jp2/nw2t93AQBaymXIslR4K8krhqlv7qakNHODqGy5bc9gtiPjofs7VwAXDKELPy1ppH1J+upsEW0jsx7t8zszmFKIGJQE6p6r09SawNkQc+j/3AEw/Q59ch5Gd9fZ9gO81ak2KwDmla7TonEOBXzqVDgCwKz5w67IcdXSImZvMY2jvcGPTE/jAmLZ9jPzTqMAgzGN5E3ma3OivTsTP3MAYEoxZX5jRsm9zfp9ujw8ExN5vPY/NQLVSjC3raU+F3zKsxwA4DEw4lCz5gERgFlzvXfc2C4Afn5+3mGhQKwQ6vYKUQEEApi7zBQBcJdnBTKuCIBAAuUuM0UA3OVZgYwrAiCQQLnLTAEAQL407tTh8/hM5hNtm00cvvX1jjsg8HoA6NZt6m3knNQggmwbMhoOY+emTzGc2MJs6hAZ4MSFlwNAfdyhxYHxROgsu3HZ9/2lsjmxNYtT9Hj4sZcDMN0M2U0qWYEiAL4JgLMvfnjwig8NITgFoD4+SV7bgNfbPbUfYW7TICwA6I9PEtD2To2TXURzO2h8zk5AAFBb0dJRLdGIweeRAIEAMIGhhk9Qhl2ocrh/kEfP+MhQ3g8A/dVuAQr/Jl8ki3v6eMfSywFgdyBnnZ1+4rx+ds67bwUxoJcDIAgfCtpIEQBBh4+78SIA3H0o6BFEAAQdPu7GiwBw96GgRxABEHT4uBsvAsDdh4IeQQRA0OHjbrwIAHcfCnoEEQBBh4+78SIA3H0o6BFEAAQdPu7G/wsuI0SPhiPUvgAAAABJRU5ErkJggg==\" />",
      "OPT2": "<img alt=\"\" src=\"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAAHUAAAA/CAYAAADex4e2AAAK30lEQVR4Xu1cfUxU2RX/6Zp2s6sbQrqtaDZN1AAaN2bDKEu3WRFXI7UEOxNla/kwzC5QZUVZPgShdQMun1E+tAXtUESx0gQiUtgN6ChNqBWhcSvdAlrC1qyjsWv8YLd2a2nvve/NOMwH896beTNvpu/9OfPm3nPP75xzz7n3d2bOf8kD9QkoDcxRQQ0oPNliVFADD1MV1ADEVAVVBTUQNRCAa1L3VBXUANRAAC5J9VQV1ADUQAAuSfVUFdQA1EAALsmPPPURxjvKkd6pwekTWoQoBYypUXSUFKAzsg4ntK8oQio/AvUWOlLWQYdK3FYSqKYOpCzKA9ovqqCKN2kO1MyFxzBaEYOXxA8gzy8YqB9i4YWPURHzLXnmEDmqjzyVD6W6MlwiAockH8KJ/XpsCH0epuE21OTko/KSiX6BQ2fLkbXmRdykoZd/H1iKZDk8g4XSLOgqe4lUK5FcVY39GRsQOv+pY7lWPMRZy/tU8+lov30E2pB5ImHw7Os+AXV6vAmx0X9C+tVD0C5+gtGmQlQF5cMQdRX6miAcpp44NYKmXT+G/s5ejH2UitC5nKfmvdqG0ZwIeF5tTzDelIzogbdx9bgWi7+i8/8aQeUV0OKcc7nuUk+tx6tDXciJmO9ZdCSOJgJU4l19BhxMyUYLcaKZljyXn55YdEcmFukaHYgTgui8I2gs3oJQDKE6bieub85G/JLngaCV2BgTivkgcxgvYuT+DXTuzuXmWVqFodEcRMxzB1R+P275mwO5NiKvvRbF2lBguBZxcdewuS4eS+Y+R8Rah5hQGuhnkeueH4PKvCv9FvJPFyCGpJ4mYxm2rz+AsdR2zrLNuFK1PR1GdXgc+gqN+Cg1HHPxNUyDx7Fvy0HcKTV/Rt6bGoex98+YvHIcRcjC+cgevKW7gSTDe9gW+z2gVQdNw2YPgMph+XS4GuGaQRSOtSCVhHpMmzBYuw9bsv+JUvNnmCZi/R69Izdwpb4ZKP4tdj8ow2pncvkvqNN4ZCzB3gepMFjS9n/AmL8J6ys19vvIIyPyw0lGeMo6eXiW6Hyqv4X3zy1Hbc4a5p2jTXsR07Ycpeu6oa+LwoXRUkR/eRm1+zKQPZAyA1TdnUI+HIuNTXQNRQhPJGKR8WNe4q3Qkuh0Qj9Zh3OrCkgYDSIGR8PvDrSt/SVK7uch8pATuRiombhjsDJWsaJ5+H0R4dd25ikMV8dBkxtmByrz6rBBpFsnDVODJORuR1/S79Ad+witNcXYwRISGpYrUL1nK8IetmFXzA4SdklIbM5BpOlD6ApIKsVCcDbCbp7kvgcxLuNhpIaLyYG5PTOs/22rkoh4JQ25mstIGvsVYh93PkvSQGUowZ4kDRaM8/M6lCsNL7YQo9Q3AcnNMB5NQvh867DlYcQEDOcGqLynXttp4zm8R6QFo4vthTTKDeIkBXFwE4a6shDhk0Vz8qa93MgnWmRLYJn2BxjcfBpdLGoExiMZ1OnPO/Du6iYs7zrFhSvLY/aIDehd+0ekEAs2zSgPbKx4+jN0vKtD4xun+P1XJsVOj6Ipdiv6E0qxtr8I+pYRVjJVndiPd4LPQaPJxcw0yiqx84kRSteDNFAZEDvQ+UY9jqautLFw6hHxqAgzCADpa3zeUYDU+n5cX1Pp5qECb0x6wGBJeqwUw/b5BoRd4pMkW52x5C4d947RPCAYU6M05NZj4Yy8QLqivflLCaA+IHvpLtQFFzgAlIjOPEKPsfxO1ycsVNFbP8GP8v+FxIpvo4fVo1KXTw0km2Spk8geso0eRCxWG99EvnWSZD0VS5h6EW/OAxjIFQjucWIEUsX0wu9Egkoz1Z+hCu+g1s5DeWmZR5Tg5S5XxTg1jgO4uO4AchYZkRIxhBRnCndbEfb7vL2jknInAWijecCTcfQ1NOPikmQUasP9bq8VDiqr6YpQ/B9yFOY0qeCVt/6mVd3nCBGadR7Brouv4ygdS3avcJbUmWWzPTQhmS+rlTciIuQbbpuUtwcQCCr1qkRSvnQ7li+5nZQJG3GblTikBDE/7HMH12QsRMdA38uOpvhHpvNcZjAa5FqyIEfz8EeEYxncvm4+lKhaPLOm9TY6EucTCKrE0R3+jO59xSjBTvxC+11y2kQfruZNQLVM57qu5HeQ3Nnusa6GUND3XgeVlUKpn2Fnu3W9yoe/TuLtvrgrnZH5ctdnLhMrBYFoK4p3QWWlUBqu/KTVLjNm57Jx93FMtmTJOQrcCdjHSOBLoWnTADmiLMJIfDOOW6KJglG0Ec2LoM68KVlaNcSHWtskxct3knZ7LtFQdB6aq/cgKSKE3x78B1AqqRdB9S/F+LO0Kqj+jJ4T2QWBOmfOnABcuvxL8lWTviBQ5V++OoMnNaCC6kltKmQsFVSFAOFJMRQEKuUGnUVJuhGRp2t8TrN0rWTlyqsgUM31KiG7K4A76xpU5cqrPFAzgxnxzEIMc61dH73Bg6pAeWUC1RyaMi1Me0obydgQihfMfCUzC/5QA8qzorDgJg29/PsUJmc3PHJB6Iyd/8JdDJ+sQc6OSr6b4AjOluux4nGPb+WdRQ/ygMqu1hIxkN5Ozk5fwVeUGlK1AOWG1bhMOEtBh4uJJ05x1FD9Y/7udR5HBM9bxlNC5ULP0bjO2PkHEXX556gJyrWiuBTw3OVluOszeWfXjXhQ2ZWUjtA0HTzRBWhv3Adt6DS7f427Ho26+CXk/DQYKze+SXpSKH+bEqVvY6KzDLmU/IVoVLGWBdJHI4uS3GTnM8L5CO5PdGJ3bgsh0VHGKj23XoV7ssjrvjGLB5XNyXN++5Is9FDuZoOQry29L/Q9vl1h8g+oL3oOhedfw5m3sjCR9AH2bPshYtGKFZpuZMgKKqckSez8whpEnkmFbuIHMOzZhthY0jSwQoOGjIAElaOHJJJe0WdthVaJw6eJmHz/PFbVZhKOLzEBxszrRlRpOKr1PdDRtr/of/MtD38nRDErT9Xdd8wGtDNg6oE/xcTuMwIakySy86PSsa46DXW6C2Sd38eXrHUkEwPZVqAKltd9DxQ6gjRPNXNo03usGm15ykufFmPdsXjc+iy5sFxlhX2BZtrJ1vIFY+WXRU4gUXeA8G35EBw2yXW6kdiebPiNY7aiZWViQJXKzg/Hw2aOfW+i13FlkTAl6lBAqDEsBGd8Ey2C5RUKifvvSQPVljFIOD1chvgXbHZAz3RfTEcjiAH1/4edTzUlCVSOKTCAhN7X0Z+SxloOnzUO2/S3yMbAFwGqU3b+XkR+shdvWpPlmP2Y2xv9jx4qEVR+f6pYhksuydeeZODP1vvKe7Kll9XGs12w82dSafhSq+g7fskklAiqDZ1yttjqUQa+7UTCPXV2Epk96Y2BXBjsZseAPJuOkFElhF/b/cnZNHIz8IWC6oqdb01PfQ1PxvvQYBjCEv17pN4W0yopRN3eeUc8qCyUJeKadUe4nazeYOALBdUVO9/mcIJkuawmjYtAiOS+Hu+A52wWUaByBbx1y58T5p9XGPgCQBXCzrdp6DIfolQtrHWzC893wIoCVZiYSmTgzyK5XRLlY2K5MCXP+pbHQVUkA38WFdiTyEUkgh4AQI4hPAuqQhn4zhXHnzS1beLPsPl/kdn+V8T30/948r+ON4kljTMVKZSB78pLZ+QI5j8VSfDLFkbzUj3rqXLEEnVM0RpQQRWtMuX/QAVV+RiJllAFVbTKlP8DFVTlYyRawv8B1hcwreqxI7wAAAAASUVORK5CYII=\" />",
      "OPT3": "<img alt=\"\" src=\"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAAHoAAABBCAYAAAAe5LCKAAAIiElEQVR4Xu2bf0xUxxbHv7RNQwwag68JSzGNShZeg5oGkNZGRV4hJS1FIRRrARtWhVREy++3ir/wRYENSGmbWoUqYismUPEXzWL5UWNLt6BVaLMQMLYN0qQP2lBSmz6z7cy9C28XFvaO7MJe78yfd8+dOXM+d875zty7bn+RBt4e+gi4cdAPPWNhghy0Mjhz0ArhzEFz0EqJgELmyWs0B62QCChkmnxFc9AKiYBCpslXNAetkAgoZJp8RXPQComAQqbJVzQHrZAIKGSazCu6s7MTra2tCgmP9GlGRkZiyZIl0m+YYUtm0Dk5OaiursbChQtn2FXXHm7z5s3YsmWLyzrJDDo8PBwrV67E/v37XXZS3LGJEWAGvXz5chQXFyMiIoLHU0YRYAbt5uaG3t5el65HMor/jLnKBLqrqwtLly4F/55wxvg4bCAm0PX19dizZw9u3rzpMAdsd2TCSM85FKQ0IeSjI4hRPebk8aR276p+2fefCfTevXtx48YNnD9/3n7P07K4j4G6NHjHArV333Eh0K7ql/1gM4GOi4vDokWLUFRUZL/naVmYA5rmic+MBxE275Fp9ea4m13VL/szZAIdEhICrVaL6Oho+z2PWQyjp+4wUmIPoYVcUyWV4OQuDcLV82AaMODUkXy8UaQnvwQgqeR9HN7xHOb20rSdhqKWAbGXpFrcPRkDFcOo9k1H07B5HFUSik/uQmq4GnNm1S/7nj+IBRNoqrjpyVhAQIDksUw9lYgMvY6Ur0sQ8+QfMFZqUTw/FxUxQJ2mEvNL88mKHSHX30KY5jcc7K5CsvoxMXXn+KLdmIVAZ5RokxGVkQm4llKLYzEL8bvxFLYVz8XhimB8OZt+SY4sm6Fk0P39/fDx8bFQ3KP16qiNEVUIzXkHR/PXQY126KLeROdLGYhe7A7MD0BEmBoeoCvqc+i77uJ2/SFkV3WRfkJR3H4BWYHu0wM9UIdNpMBX2YpF6L9RezQPMWoTOnQJiOoMxdvRi/EIPBEQsRpqDzjPLzY2DrWWDFqv1yM7O3ui4r7fAZ1/FBq1TWhI9icB+xMDhmPIW/cf/HRw9BrxeaQHTfpbuPPVMexGLr5N/xVZwWm4nbgfO199GZE4jaeDLiHVEaCFEI0QkFEIakxEd0My1KTMmwauoSwvFRk/vTV2DSClpakZXXe+QPnuR6G98gzOvLDDiX45lJ/kziSDnlRxDzch1z8HqP4UhWH/MA/8I+o2rUWa1wf4TvMjMs//E2VZK8gqHhZTdM3zuFIwhFdCziD2M3Jf6P9gKMvDuowfkGEJOnYIFUIqJ5mAuf0XTbkvIgFFMBaGYZ5wv4WY+i4BdzKvYHlZGgLpKqapO+wSnjvoD53mshP9Yp6IQ26QDDopKQleXl4TFLdQg/0MSLHcBo0YSLreiMbEi7gUOYzTY4KLpvRC6HbGI3BuDyq3vQZN1aBw7VDIbSTE7kPfaPr2u2P+nWixio/xbnIAeVAYmlCD49CachknSQ0W269Cug5qjEH3pUj8dvoIst4oEkQicQIndDuR6DeIE870i2EKjjSVDNq24jZhuGk3/Ld64oJZNI0pacOLaL+wg6yWWdoaCZmmAE9coDWfPCKmAXScomC/xUvt1eTafEfG0eX7mgD61q1boOqaHnVaNg8PDzQ3NyM4ONji8h/oqUyCX2s49GvasImo1QG6TSrWYVdqOBE21pBN/XXYEnwGz7c8aDqWHk8x01xDvP5ZtG7aiiqyUxO2dnmBuBm1Btl94/oaE2likn/YmhXoc+fOYf369Vi2bJmV6BoaGsKCBQtsnHHTOhiNQr8KsxCbIjym71H35jaUd/6CFQX1FvX8wUIqgiyFT+1Fsj16iohAy2bONIW+aDELMetRRKEW9XO+WL9HuoQysdurzKKeP5hfrnqXFWi6krdv347y8nK0tbWBpmvaqOJOT0+H0Wi0nodQBzXozrUHjgZ+H+KuryJ6W4dCzzL7D8aUESNbs44yRAVVYrFN0GKmCe1OnQQcFYvrUR/9ibl+U/Cx0E7bL1fFPMkf4VUqFVatWoWzZ88KnpeWlqKhoUEAbtXG18HJ5knF2bY2rH03Fd76dAR+9aqTV46ouLc+cRTGrEBMOG8RtoRZQA2t3yb0NJ5ARbMPNFqy758tTeHkZ8SmGCspKUFmZia6u7uhVquF1ezu7j5OcZvT4796zadZk22BqNLdh+a1+wQBdL9DB3+tJy7bTKkOmq3wACbgG8t9vGXXVgcqdCcg7uWjAlXjSoCD/HGBbmyCvnfvHubMmYP8/HwcOHBASOEZGRmIj483u2w+jMhu+f8UJjmPFmupBta5IMVpb6WEBykom2zTRtvEscRj2V7kCi9MyN5aOOD5EF5WZwEuQMeBLky6vaIfuh0/fhyDg4PC1yQ0bVsrbgleCALsPSC/gJxzPy7eYJU2mXbGEgaUYmJLqI2v2VL6kZfNpKD7+vrg6+sLmsbpamb/quRP9NflIPn2RtQKp2KjbbaDOk5xU7cki0p5wbX0dsoDk9WrV+Pq1avw8/ObqLjtzFnYM69px+vXx79PthHomYyfAPVl1MRfFJU/OUihx68bu6LReiwGT87S+Y6zQzAl6JqaGmzYsAH0E98Jinsqz6zEzugbKbqmxTPw2CpzBXXKe+apHLOhLRCBnBMF2Jm4AqqHFDKNiN0jUG9vbyQkkFcDTv+qxNnPtLL7twvaYDAICpzlYwNlh9Q1Z28XtGu6zb1ijQAHzRoxmdpz0DIFx+o2B80aMZnac9AyBcfqNgfNGjGZ2nPQMgXH6jYHzRoxmdpz0DIFx+o2B80aMZnac9AyBcfqNgfNGjGZ2nPQMgXH6jYHzRoxmdpz0DIFx+o2B80aMZnac9AyBcfqNgfNGjGZ2nPQMgXH6jYHzRoxmdpz0DIFx+r23/7Dh3otNxZEAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC\" />",
      "OPT4": "<img alt=\"\" src=\"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAAGsAAABxCAYAAADS8l3xAAANEUlEQVR4Xu2de1AV1x3Hv6aZTqZRh6FJK9pOO+ogZnQ6EYRYmwTx0TgGMdxRUsPD4VahQoUYHorSoQNGEaooan3MpYiPijMQEdEU9CKdsUYCtFGSADGUNKOYsTFGacemzm3P2d0Le6932cfdu3vXu/dP2HP2t7/PefzOOb/f74z5H/nB/BlCA2NMWIbgxAhpwjIOKxOWgViZsExYRtKAgWQ15ywTloE0YCBRzZ5lwhLSgANDfadQnGZH1PEKxIc8aQBV3UNf/TakNUTg+OF4hOgoscY96yEG6zMx0QLU3dxjEFifoz5lHizYjpsBCSszGBd6ShAz/gkd26nUV7OwMiccRE9pDMZLLeaD57zoWc4hLRPbLw4CIckoO7wJ6QtD8Z3BdhypKMSq7c1E5BlI3rEf27LmYNx1OgRyz9OPSa7TuLVyQ5plKy6S14ck78DhTVYsDB0Ph0eZZ+L+KTIEcs8DU4jIrTgc/0MfoBCvUjksRw+qFifiUlodDhHh/91zBBll47DNNhuXrVUI2llIes4QeqreRIz1Pkp6a5Aa+iQ7DOZNRUdPDsI1nrIcfVVYHN2FtPd3IH7SAyJbAcqC8mGLB+oFZb7N9Ky8mbXoyQmHxiK7EPQMa7AeKWRiqfEEO3oj6g5sQHyoA53liYi9Fo3dcZPxBIIxY9FLCB0LYkT8Gc3dN9HfsBW5Nd2klmiUdTQiJ/wpH8FyzoUHPEgcgui8PThQuAyh6EB57FpcW7IecZOfAoJmYFFMKMaCjhJCMn/l57CYTx4iMGIR0ZKE3nOpCCXTi2PwEnZtSMf6W28O/w0gQ4u9Fd0Df0Hl5m+h4PzzOLEgC/1Jv0X2ilexGMfwXEQT0n0Ki2P0sBPlYbFoKbDjXGoYaUDfYLD9EDYs24JbJc6/0U/rg735KgauHMJm5OPDdXeRMztTQGZDwPon7PmvIJFYQSMTK9eCqYHwUSIG3jqPn+zKRDjtTXQYjGnCnJIwlFvPwnLhXZRG/xftuzZg2fp/YD0fluUObMywSFq3mr97duSH5QFHybtjnuFqHjEQPrJ+jrdOT8eunEjSm+6xQ3TtXJwvvoOlUScEZGZhWW4V8BqomkJLr0t4zmLmpOVoSzvLm1DvMkNfREs8epsW4/6xCuSs2s5M1mSsQXV5NpKmfYnqjF/AWvMl+VMptkb1I9FShE+dQ+G0AVQx/yf2he2P2Js6gyhOnR8zJ01rRxp/WTDUToa+lWhJOoOmxfdwbNjwocNjKcqzExA+ro+TyZPMDUh/+h3SEFeRaSEVNvtOpIbpYxMKw2JaaTGebaRzDVGnYxCdRyicD7Gk4yj5W5A6GlatFgfu2TcjbE0wGjnjZdjCa38FHY1ZZAQwwlJBWCGCsNhWegkJzS+gLWUNahjrfMTUVU3HqlX0AH1VyZjWthDNL7+HFGLdDdJlQ1k5Nv0yGKcjIpH7qdvLho0lfXqK3E8XgMW10tKpuMgZF3IrVv48t2NQ467ZkRqnlHV4MKPpHBuH0mk2zrhwl4A1mGJvF7Jz8FA3M/RtnrBL98WuVF0JwGJbaXRvumE+BMwca0VvfgPPuOCrgTaC19AQ9w43B1N4FhQE7xKAK1WF2j0nAIu1BNc8e0DaQtDxGepXW3Bg7lH9Ptx9jnXXIWPW5wC1dA52oK+lGrbWH8BaQNZfBpnLPMNiPjwRf+OvTQQb0De4Ub8RqZVtuBbJN/O1a3HE+mGNi/nXuZ0SD0sCl4U+tQTZdWBseAhZjxnj9wish53lCIvIJaa285c2+g45Bbv8A7yW/x8kln4PZzWf47jFey6zgGB/HvYc2a2m68hnNpDJepFZLP8BE1zWZP4NTfneIPNddN1VhNZ5RciZaEdKeAdS/HI33ZPB5D6H+TcoKp0XsMh+WuceZLS+gL10R4CZE0oRfNYHOxNe69HNEqT1iRokXr9U9QqUw2I+NgbWZrIAG/7pe4QgqB1G1ldRm3CGNYDIAp9ug63sjkPboXhMMsikpRAWNSoKUYy12Bf/I26CZltvAsqlWZCqtzuhCj3MaViEvOpiZCdFIsQgoBQPg44b9Vid+hnW1vG3cLhN3oZFGh8oakZd9xfJ71nMmmoNrrxx7JHFJ2NJxt7BQb80MnTXtdcCyITluhU0su3jfvgnYu57LXZgViATVmAqyV++2gXWmDFj/EUuw8ihZSyi2bMM0yy8WhQb6CsfE1F16lnUf68ap8l6Jz0+TLVjfe+YEJ+MwzY0T38dmZH+ubmrPSzHDdiLDmBgZY5uvgzCUIk3lH03KgZeQaGKviHeNaKR0trC8mtQTqX4LzANYXnaolKrzUmoZ6gH9cUb0RC1W4L7M+80wY8cgzSDxWxRpd1F/mnWYVTzH3P4SHwKpfqqc+d0K1y21DSX2uWFGsGiPh0ZKA36DfGLd278avzhDKy3MYE6nw47gI4mA+1dWTg563cSn/f992gDizmi2IOgarUC6ISiQYgvfWctKnLyhyNbdpAokKznvsap4ixYmKgW+pO2HUZPl5fafozjOof6OJuBNrBoq151F5tUOvIXjAaZ8z6sFUHYyXM1szr98r+gPasSMxk3bok+wHQonHUeP+/yj1gyDWCxR+qz/rQAXaIt1NtoEC5I4s4naFiXyzimYkoZG150WwEsZkQoBipt6vvlKxg1NYBFAWRj1d1M6W5qiqJBsnA+6iwWWD5Bku3XWLH4p8AxCyL2L1EOC9Qlby26VlRJ740KIEgtogEselL7OnZP/r0Ek5kTW1E0yHSUzGuCdfccJgQ2+l+X2fCkSyk8WJm4ZeOF/ohqSYHsonUqf0AjWKnEqton2apSFg2yHNO+rmWjPQbpsX0OogbfhmXjRW4oXIOna2gUZhVxVauGfW8SwkSdO6kVm4YtQSXSG5pyFqIlNYBFDyx/hf51JyQOJf4UDcLOoS/2r/YLvxI/hDVKNEj6Qo1dnQMO1hXkTV2Kj4uuojHx+6JdHcykPlo0iIQqVHvkAT7IC8fsjzfiXmMiVI7TlC2lBj1LJiy/cr40YY3eosSiQdxKM3uOs09g7kVfeAKbsEaBJSEahF+ausWtzUDlta8QWSwUlyV7tOEVMGEJaE9aNMhIYQq2CMu7XiTJEcpR6pOgOBOWN019pCyNws94D/P2pmNi8zqEX1nhgyhNQ8Iip6edzTh3shWwbpG5TyZ3nSWFpevhIOMJXBDsg9gww5nufC9caUcLrupWHxa7w2GF88BDzrGHlKYw8ozhYFHRvckTqDIsxqjYBxQWk2RZ32b16hIvLPH4QxI1E5YkNXl+iPpx5CG1fyXqmJQ+zp+vohhNWIphMWuqlzvwxiOHgR4iGxW/hV/wMYHlGOxE47mTqGibisK4v6PYQ8JF9rNVGgZdou2dKfFo33JLcqJqwknDw6rAnMvZJM8tl9uPZPBk/Bwiv4sv7Fuxcn4RevMu8MxolWCp0lPkVmJ4WFwiYmZbaD62L+SlTmUm+gjkzuWnUxWHpXf0inAkyOMCyxMYhbDktnftng84WDJ33bUjIeFNhtzB4A4ErRjJwDnaMDjFxst6KT4MStCaTo8Yrme5p5QLR3JyCGpqzvAUyO1skCCekUTIzt2OQZnH+j7iIsvX3SmD4WB5qzw/6Vlyfd3ZrRHTB8Nb/IrKy/Z1N2Ep0vOjhbTxdTd7lgq4NPN1N4dBFWgx6b893Xygsq+7CWs0WBIDE5yetC43H/jC1900MMS7lkhgQtPPriDtkZsPfOHrHnCwFOxgiAUmZI9FwyM3H/jG19108hTpW2KBCeylMFr8DLnd5I1i5PYsfwpMMGGJkBcOTNgQdRWxL+XxMmPTqnj3Y4mG8MhtdCYsEY2JBCYwxkcabh+kUffB3FVQlT5K+W3CGh2WWGACs23UjDjntUs+zXodcLBkbuSKBCYwDp0J5JYKGtT9oA8t+6vROjkZBT5J2BVwprscWGKBCe6LZhKOygR7L0J4COdDKHdaGvX5gINF3cSkxBRLCUxwu32Iy8++rGwSjvokiXLAxRSrGfHuwfhwn8NU7Vlqyu69YBpEPirIgyH0XS6WIHsBp+uFMGovlQMuD4acDDMihiITkPAuEribWNmreDejO67aNwm8Ai/DDAGgRu4mp5sb/3ZB5w2uvroDi1qmc7uw4q/a31buqdlqMAzSsUrtrGjej/9SaqDLhOdPzsIl0ZxTUmrz/hltYMEP8g3K1lWg5huknUvvTJ5yYQVuJk+qKZ1z5MqCFeA5clk725/ThDtpmtmnR9q1XwPzX1BUgRoZGO5jkH/emEBvcWgKsiArZpJGJ9Gyxma9YMkT0nya1YBOPctUvxINmLCUaE2nMiYsnRSv5LUmLCVa06mMCUsnxSt5rQlLidZ0KmPC0knxSl5rwlKiNZ3KmLB0UryS15qwlGhNpzImLJ0Ur+S1JiwlWtOpjAlLJ8Urea0JS4nWdCpjwtJJ8Upea8JSojWdypiwdFK8ktf+H1augETei0yKAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC\" />",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "9m/iwvJKC6coEJr5HJJczQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "9m/iwvJKC6coEJr5HJJczQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.66",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu23": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>A mixture of 40 mol % A and 60 mol% B is being flash distilled at a rate of 10 kmol/hour at 1 atm total pressure. The liquid product should not contain more than 30 mol % A. The relative volatility\u00a0of A in the mixture is 2.5. The amount of top product (in mol/hr) is</p>",
      "OPT1": "4.61",
      "OPT2": "5.39",
      "OPT3": "6.41",
      "OPT4": "9.35",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Dsdj/LJX8pBs6q+b96fwiQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Dsdj/LJX8pBs6q+b96fwiQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.66",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu24": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>A binary distillation column is operating under conditions specified below:<br />\r\nFeed rate = 350 kmol/hr, Overhead product rate = 150 kmol/hr<br />\r\nMole fraction of more volatile component in,<br />\r\nOverhead product = 0.97<br />\r\nBottom product = 0.02<br />\r\nBottom product rate = 200 kmol/hr<br />\r\nReflux ratio = 3.5<br />\r\nIn the stripping section it was observed that the mole fraction of the volatile component in the<br />\r\nvapour leaving a plate is 0.33 while it\u2019s mole fraction in the liquid coming to the same plate is 0.25.<br />\r\nAssuming constant molal counter flow, the condition of feed is</p>",
      "OPT1": "Saturated liquid",
      "OPT2": "Saturated vapor",
      "OPT3": "Superheated vapor",
      "OPT4": "Partially vapor",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Wkw/v0ACIC+JhZVbmq0HcA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Wkw/v0ACIC+JhZVbmq0HcA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.66",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu25": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>A slab to paper pulp 1.5 m \u00d7 1.5 m \u00d7 5 mm is said to be dried under constant drying conditions from 65% to 30% moisture (wet basis) and the critical moisture is 1.67 (kg free water)/kg dry pulp. The drying rate at the critical point has been estimated to be 1.40 kg/m3.hr. The dry weight<br />\r\nof each slab is 2.5 kg. Assuming drying to take place from the two large faces only. The drying time required is _______ (in hours). (Rounded off to 2 decimal place)</p>",
      "OPT1": "0.975",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "VoIzYEjzbiY1r007lUT01w==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "5kxMa8YwwyHwJY15nzG3sQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "2",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "Alphanumeric",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu26": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>Sulphur dioxide is absorbed from air in a packed absorption tower. At a certain location in the tower, the mass transfer flux is 0.027 kmol/SO<sub>2</sub>/(m<sup>2</sup>.h) and the liquid phase concentrations in mole fraction are 0.003 and 0.0003 respectively at the two phase interface and in the bulk liquid.<br />\r\nThe diffusivity of SO<sub>2</sub> in water is 1.5 \u00d7 10<sup>\u20139</sup> m<sup>2</sup>/s. The film thickness is given by A \u00d7 10<sup>\u20133</sup> mm, the value of A is ________. (Rounded off 3 decimal places)</p>",
      "OPT1": "30",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "ryC6LDGQWsjSK1ltmcPebA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "5kxMa8YwwyHwJY15nzG3sQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "2",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "Alphanumeric",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu27": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>Oxygen (A) is diffusing through methane (B) and hydrogen (C) present in the volume ratio of 2 : 1.<br />\r\nHere, both methane and hydrogen are non-diffusing. The diffusivity are given as</p>\r\n\r\n<div>\u00a0</div>\r\n\r\n<div><img alt=\"\" src=\"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAAQsAAABICAYAAADh7tAkAAAV+0lEQVR4Xu1dbVBUV5p+ZtadSaXUTaWSDWh2ZypkgVTp1AZQ19KKpBGjiSgDiRr5MvSkcAMRpWgQbZLMgCgfg4g4q7EaBcREZ5pIMIUjkWAqZmoJpDKrWwOsSa2ZKBpd1g+ym3Jdds85997m3ube7tsft2nsc3/2/TjnPOe9z3nf531vnx/8HznAD44AR4Aj4AaBH3Cy4DbCEeAI6EGAk4UelPg1HAGOADhZcCMwCIE/oy3rWaQ2fyl7fgQy7R+hKeVv/N7m2HAvWupKsaHqNHl2OOKLGnCgNBmR03/o97ZC9YGcLEJ15g0f9w10F1fj5uYdSAmfZnBro+ivyYc95lcoNz2Ka70HsTU5D10ZZzBQacJMg1sPlcdzsgiVmQ74OOkLXIVLaW8EgCyIF7OtB3PKMxDJHAlKVMuRYF+HvoFCxBrNVQHHdnIa5GQxObiHQKs0DPlHtOM7NDf3kPHOQWZ1DbZvTAxAaECJKglxXRkY7MwWCSQEIDd4iJwsDAY4dB9PyKK4ETBvQUrkAxju3on1CQeA6hPoKJyP6UYCMzaAxhUrcWztSXRmR4OrFv4Bm5OFf3DkT3GLQKBCg7u43FaAJe3zcHJfBqJdCZy3u1EcvR9RPc3IJoTGD9cIOJHFPQy35WFWKlkBVA+qMpej1PwiTJFcNnIF7dhwPzo6T+LTkWg8t2qFBl63MdRlw46sAjQP06c5u+ruzvvBvEeH0H3qfTRtuojV/Q1KfYGc69q/A1mWZtDuhWfWomm7GYls7tWyHVJ/4lHd14HCWLn/EJjQYOxyG17NPo+0wyUwhf/IBUDfY6gxE/GDG7kIqtOM1D0LxrhFwJFTqDQ9Ij6KGG7372Ars6KqJ4YYwxFiDA/pbCaULiM4te3C6+2zUbbrVczXNFhhBZyX+m/IsO9BacoTuKNQ8Rfjjsvzvqj8dzHcfxqdx/fCenUOXv76HdQObsCZgXKYZopO+9gltL26Enn3CtFNVujIO2dgXZ+FnbCgryMfsS5TkmMYHerF4IwYxDrGT8nleeydazMsDBkb7oJ1ay+W7rK4IQpijyxUKcFIxSFuxzpfT3WyGG5D1qx3sWRwonvGmHteKhoT7bjSlEIy2vwYR0AkgL0R6HD3QjFCTkAVeXnGRTjRVa96ArZ/zsRgcpL2eZW50T8TlCw+wp9mLCQezy2hHuLcRkXmYGyoESuifoO/PyMtGGO43W1FdMJpZDh+026R3r9qx1+ghoUCo4xAc/Y+ihp3uOgfhOJKRhQbPkBcYxVSZrvyKOht4lgqn0QPF0B1I65KFvf6axC9FjimmnYKVOypewxBc6FApBV4ROGRaXSPEXIqzlX3YaAwFkJ2TwoDB1Ftz8D5VLP2eYWbf5Oo/7mof7gE+7LnKMXDscvotm5Ba1w1Dqb8REXsE8MJBVkILnqUGbDJSEkgEDO+VPRZY3ys3Wwk7KRFUgZnQkZ7UZOUDEsPi+Vkh1YRGLXhNLQueFsDk6AxqaDqiApZiAbbvkzDcxBjz/0v8By2YirFF8w6C7ZDT+DsK/mCDhFfhMM1m5ERG658USUD/1G5zLOQXtLrqD6zDSjLgkXrvLMmMHoBjbmv4+ySveOEMTqAtrI30B6Wj135ixCumhZQIwtxji1RsF+R6RiqBOcve6ahy8c4/UknGr9dgJIft+OlAqqVLEMRCdO2L7yN9xwVmsJvpSnRXmVVGOnFX0SxPOyShjE2jP6WOhRuqEIP/S08E9VN27ExMdKrtvyFTjA8R4UsBIN9fqRYtuLJuyp6Fl+8Jho5neQeHLdVwsxKbYUjPLMa9VmrsNzkZ5BFg212tJQzbtCuznmC9oTnON+sIuCxGNgE8+m5MkOmK3464mp/ptQD2OOcNYtIYOgEynLyiCYURTQhO16+9IZM03A+7ywgkkfKCWMNcNyZPFQxCAaykMiJvZ6EYN/CmaNEoHxsmOkmqY0XiD0dVmonPYsVXo/+6aX2bUbOSL6KdiKGJ+m30fBZLQlnpmF0oAW51TOwy8ZDbhWyoMbzc7Svfk+9hl+MtVtYKe1ifEfz5+lf4YWGTUhLjmWrF80EnGitR57lcyTa3pnoGuufWfUrpRczrGGi9+PqnK/turr/Xj9qouNgiZBrEFJY0YcitTifrGK9e7YiWVpBD7+GqH8pg/mdZQK5TL/m+rwkRsr7xQjjZZgJm2bqwj4YyEIYAAt/4yykFkMKzST8PpR9UyIRC71MhTDdzbHLdKlEFpdRwL2JCUhOJAtm9IVEsFCbCHE1zANj3uTvjpAYtg2JqpkRcVVlc+/vzIlo4KhSCZVcnXNnST6cl8hikVz4dUMWzs0xQ05Hb4FG4ZK78/R5fiWLR1U0iwqEGfQx2ESykAhkPxY52vSFLAQyiGmNw9mDKZitFpbRMKTjHP746UHRUzZYb/HB5AJ96wSyEESsXuTIY1WxV4KA9yZhipNEGHoMF6kIdmy5dkmt6IXYC+Qinj+GaDBZeBOGSN8jtIheAVv1JR3jr2Fnbq0rlV4g16TzLzF3e2Ixkbvz/gxD1DIf0m8XUe5TJkZ7/j3zLJz0FD1mxbxOMwaL22UlAa5uJCE2DUNMhzG3wwsvRk+fptA1TmQheQ4zcUSRcydse6IV9XldCGuQhCUdK7hhIYGrgiAR/cxAp3aJYfXvQRLJOqCkCUfLEzBjiBpaCb4WPYUHGRFbSYqhW1mGLIYj678wqVcdujvv8Ci8EDilOTrvVGchCbDIEfSDGUMsvLFO+yU+01qVfTR8z8hC6fXoaZothDm3UKGZvqWeYDGs2CRmSUiKmYXZ1/G6W7LX04OpfY2CLKTJkv8DgTA8oj7bcvDc4qWySkTxhb26zcXHOsI1RXOPEbH07/AVzbWn7iQqs6//N+CJZ0EFWEk4JOmJ+BLYD2wl3ysYUYFK6xeOoa6wmIiUpC0nJV3w2mRkIVZPtnYCK9JUxGB35x22J6QCm6J+rZE6zUHlkzVO30loEG5EtSPLNTZ8Dnu2bkRB8wXSkpHuuJPASccV8RIyYz5H829l1sgWAJKlox+JWXrY6CP0pHHZlRSj1aiMsrn4XoTO30m01r8JCxuzINQ3bEpDsnM2a2q/91713odvQ3S42PJK0Kc+hnnrHVhoNeCtEyScycM35U4rrCv3X2bEjlJjXZoFeSnMlbhpqSD1//8pqOvfbOFfI3plLlP4JmqLMW1YcNZdODiFx2hw130gC5L1EFfKu6pfEiqrGZ++0grrhXhUsH9JElaSpOulXtble+BZUDfbOogVFatZtSnznpJG8LZajt1gsPnjJwsB/h2IP5D3iSyA2xho3AKTuRNRRZWo2bxW+BZAKmwpuYGM7t3IjnZy+VmcnI5zOXbvKui8Tp2KRnNunWFxtz8mhT/Dzwgw/WULrpfqFTb93P598jgfyYKiQD8w68T7TeWOOE/QOIphXhOv8kcnVAhsQK79KewqT9SoKnSBri9FWdRocrsQo+dDo/tkgvkwOAL+QsAPZOFJV2gqqhVlR8Ow+S0viMKTppyvpfUHZafw082b3H+R6Es7/F6OwH2KQADJghPFfWpDfFghgkCAyELMVye8JXyc4zhk33UYBDj7dJn+D4Pii0Tj/pLeoGHwx3IEJh2BAJHFpI+Td4AjwBHwEQFOFj4CyG/nCIQKApwsQmWm+Tg5Aj4iwMnCRwD57RyBUEGAk0WozDQfJ0fARwQ4WfgIIL+dIxAqCHCyCJWZ5uPkCPiIACcLHwHkt3MEQgUBThahMtN8nBwBHxHgZOEjgPx2jkCoIMDJIlRmmo+TI+AjApwsfASQ384RCBUEOFmEykzzcXIEfESAk4WPAPLbOQKhggAni1CZaT5OjoCPCHCy8BFAfjtHIFQQ4GQRKjMdrONU3f7BoD9Fct4h3dA9ZIIVcO/7xcnCe+z4nf5AgO7nseUmNgdgl/J7/buRbJ+Dg+SPoh+7Jm6g1JWkssO9PwZ2/z2Dk8X9N6dTa0R0Q+m8S0jbn8L2dTHuoFsT1qFzTh7ZbOoB0oy0d+sfUODNbuzGdTRon8zJIminJkQ6RsOQ9XYy2I/QrLLlo5EoCNt19mKbQRs9G9n3yXg2J4vJQJ23OY7AcDuK6/4X5tJkRD44jG5rNhJ2/iWq+46gMPYhA5ESt988tpxvZakTZU4WOoHilwUIAbY/bgLsBX1kM+1YTDOo2bHLbXh1yQdYdFJlxzxFm2K4UvkkejqzEflDgzo0BR7rRBY0rsvDrNQDGl2nu5+Xo9T8omw39SkwyqDsorSTWz3Or34XTWwPWI2D7KbetX8HsizNIHuzk529G3Bi16uYT7eKVBx0F/DT6LR/ipGYZVi1/BmVHeG8AYPuRP8xTr1/CJvOr0Z/k1xfoOe6sH9HobgjnXy39TGX9qS6AzrVMKKT0LXNadNsb7qtdc/YJbJBtgV9abtRbpoNl+8/2yrTjMFivvWhumch3/3c9IgIOTXu38FWZkVVT0wA3ER/WkfwPGtsuB8dncdRZ/0G81++gara/0DRmVOodODs3Ncb6C5ejvSrr4gE8T3bX3bluRdw9mAKZkuWPjqAtrI30B6Wj135izzfFlINIppq7DiJ43UHcHX+P+Drqn0YLDqj2MyardDz3sS98newLzsSd7p3Yn0CWWxUN8t2boTYVM+XmPHM0+P9ZanURsw1KgwZu0xCnTJ8uLTUPVGQ7rLNv3NuoaIjH7HTQ9itIFiokwWbsHexREX4EYwjFY2JdlxRrDDB80IGc08YWfxpBhJMT+AO8+IGCfF2kPh8unq32Uq7FuerPhr3PpzJnK2Uqdj71G/QUTgfGk/yHBZGFoOYkUA8lDsniE2k4ly1PDwQ437rk7L0o0BuCS3LdKQk6f252IEthGjmYDojvELsffQN/45DGjkjii1ojavWuSE3HctqVEbZ0Jkd7doD8RzdKXeHKlkwlXgtcGygELETgkbRGOzr0Kd6fsphMEkdlkI+N2Qh7hhvDduJ7n0ZiCarm3K1u4fLbQWYlzcTRwbKYZrpYvWjG0OnNuLhPVVOO9vTrSVbkJs/gk12jRVULJ5SkIW0mz3KZSKhSCDm665JUERdsWNceCaqm7ZjY2Kk/wjPMbs30V+TjjjLBxPnO1Nj4aOkHNOGBWdrkTLbOeSbJLOZxGZVyEI04vZlGp7DKAE9CXH7X+Bk4dPE6SQLyLZ+pC9T/RLg3x/As2kvIpZqFhKZzCnHocfP4pUCqmtQbakSNZvXCtc4DpEUVn6MJQ5hT+03lYGpkQXzeuJgWSR/2fSOy1vwaDj8IT75/Qf4dkEqftxejILmCwCrxizAwjudqCssJqEyUXd8qtAUSC9+cKMi7HI4KcO9aKkrxYaq0+yn8MxaNG03IzFyprcDC/r7VMhCAOn5kWINNVr0LL54TVxN5FoGld/oQUUuK7JWrTBQCJWJbqLwJ0xaNepTFuOndw9j3hqZUOtYPVREXK2VxeX0uRODyc0un+vBS0XCgd49O3DgKvAV0Q16sAxFh8uwOWM+HrtIYuooM07LXwzqQSQlo3b+ERVDl5PDr7EG7chVkIfGoIOBLCRy+pLNNOGCJhyl1Zikbyw0HiZ2Z5NrJ2Rv3WU271KjjIRLMFJxSCWFK+pIN7bhM6Yb3SY60jZUP1QMmyuhOujpwHUHVcjiz2jL+jnaV7+nrtCLqa2WDCJ07YxCH8mLp19ORMOmNCTHhpO4jiryJ9Fa/yYsXfNh63aXmvIGQWm1/RTzbcUwr4kXVX+JuM4g6oANG3CUvEgVCLPL4n3J/aXClcY5b3rk+T06yYLpERvwwQuHhTjb8X1DCxMR33v2Y8TF1SLCJs8e0Dl8FqldazR0A5EwTBvQjGx9cxQMZMFAFj1bCxm+Q+sRx9u8FPYrDUgJJ7GzRCyo9sIDdpculUTntPvem5Db9USyYCAXEsFCTXS7K8bHQMNnFZjz+18gqmUh+tSUYnF1s4CkqPysJLOYPWo3HrefVBGqiDHtPohb5nyYvqOiXBGgQhYkp6d9zvM334s79JEF04+SRvC2Qo8Y9+7+tWwEqxbsxyLFGANMFhHy1VvSLB4ef3G9QEf7FjWykH6L8hNZUHzT0LrgbU0hlAnVf/gcn+59Uwh5DNVb/Aqg1w+bQBbCi9iLHImhZY+W0mRoIC9p8n/j8IqVOLb2pIZSbFTtvXMY5GLsrgjBZ7IIRBhCPID+PUhKuo5SFbJIRxUGtgM7SBET8/QqTWARs6RjPN4guslyjPwYhkAt8+HB/Hhlth56Fgo9RV+D7B2Iv4hid4Kx43E0DNkCU8VT6LiPRX8nspA8Bydlnbq+J1pRn9eFsIY9KE2JxnQdL5tAPOphgL5pU7tKWDXzwt5WFZ4Ud6h+/iy/IoLIChNDFO/75smd0gr8lVOdhfQ7YGOp6++JoPwKCq9n4AAtiZ4+iqG2XcjJu4YMFuKNiSr//6DkTCOpHZhBNCdiuOZr5AMp55Jp7wVOYS7NOK+osxDJjKQiwfSDBMwYIlkVUw2m0QWFhk2eQKLrWg/JQuH16GmA4m9Gzki+i/QtsUFzHfCrnUKWhKVkSTh+LUeFnPW0OTWuUZCF8GGNBUw/UhxEULPl4LnFS8cFS/Yi5uGqIlZ2uo1ds5cU2NCQZkww8tSdRKCjan2DaPyempPoYpNV1W2dh1eeBdE9aD/b43DUkDoSLY8kXozBpzGBmbyXIlmQLyQVFZwqVbRO/9OgqcyzVGAroiaUOEskMoisz53SrxqEO159SfSj3oPYmpyHZqG81Lj0p0LgFGwtIjMTMc3N+K3D9MQFYNW3QqaGGbOErY4KFKbJ7UdUDyVq+nWqyuFYPC3CmJmg/0tsSlvplH2aGiSgt5fefxvi0tWlzYthSDqE/D/RD8xb78BCagUib50g6nUevil3Kul15QlESEKVuLLULnRf9OMxWdCV8p+QW3gIzX+7zT0Z6UWZXzdFEBBsNqY1TlkdO0V6b3Q3vScLSO7yf6mXfjtVFT5I3FPrhXhUsNSS8MInXS91H0qoETtzia24K6bOwrWcE0/Jgoqy+X9EzIp+JHRo1ZkYPSX8+ZOGAP8OxCX0PpAFfecvoDH3ZZibZzny/vTFHRMLVkqurndUHSp6wSYlHedy7F7GteOFSoOkrmI8bUv7NITu0xfxVwuX4uk7RzxInVK9phbHf/ILrLtkxSzNorRJM2XesKEIaInJhjY6pR7uG1nQodKX89T7aNokxW80RCyCrdSMNSa1sl06KQ3ItT+FXaSgRtMrcAujUJR1+pNO7DVXER1EOFhRVtbz+NnNekTJv551U5T1TQVQtu8hVFU8g+/oNxucLNzOAL8gtBDwnSw8wosKaa0oOxqGzW/5QhQeNarjYimkGpfJhJsM+uNYHT3il3AEgg2BAJJFsBKF85SIxHF2HRc4g81aeX8mFYEAkYXsYyjFcINs5Z6Qmguy/k2qqfDGQx2BAJFFqMPMx88RmPoIcLKY+nPIR8ARCAgCnCwCAjNvhCMw9RHgZDH155CPgCMQEAQ4WQQEZt4IR2DqI/D/F5yh7FO5Z6IAAAAASUVORK5CYII=\" /></div>\r\n\r\n<div>Then the effective diffusivity of \u2018A\u2019 in mixture is \u2018<em>x</em>\u2019 \u00d7 10<sup>\u20135</sup> m<sup>2</sup>/s, then the value of \u2018<em>x</em>\u2019 is _______.<br />\r\n(Rounded off 2 decimal places)</div>",
      "OPT1": "2.46",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "jjNaPQnO8mWlwErl++Y9dw==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "5kxMa8YwwyHwJY15nzG3sQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "2",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "Alphanumeric",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu28": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>Silica gel is used to adsorb moisture from an air stream in multistage counter current unit operated isothermally. The initial moisture content is 0.015 (kg water)/(kg dry air) and the final value is to be 0.0015 kg water/(kg dry air). The air is admitted at a rate of 10 kg dry air/s and dry silica gel at a rate of 0.90 kg/s. The adsorption isotherm is represented by <em>Y</em> = 0.04<em>X</em>, where <em>Y</em> is kg of water vapor per kg of dry air and X is kg of water vapor per kg of dry silica gel. The minimum\u00a0number of ideal adsorption stages by using kremser equation for above operation is ________.</p>",
      "OPT1": "3",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "I7dKpk2s37EHTIkpkYBKgA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "5kxMa8YwwyHwJY15nzG3sQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "2",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "Alphanumeric",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu29": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>The adiabatic saturation temperature of air-benzene system at 310 K is found to be 285 K at 101.3 kPa. The vapor pressure of benzene at 285 K is 6.7 kPa. The humid heat of the system may be taken to be constant at 1.155 kJ/kg K and the latent heat of vaporization of benzene at 285 K is<br />\r\n435.4 kJ/kg. The benzene content in the air at 310 K is ________. (kg benzene vapor/kg of dry air)<br />\r\n(Rounded off 2 decimal places)</p>",
      "OPT1": "0.124",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Z3wjWZaKleNeHxmQQBttaA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "5kxMa8YwwyHwJY15nzG3sQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "2",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "Alphanumeric",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu30": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>A solution of 5 wt% Benzene in toluene is to be extracted with water in a cross current unit using 20 kg water in each stage for 80 kg feed. The equilibrium relation is Y = 2.2X where Y is kg benzene/(kg water) and X is kg benzene per kg toluene. The minimum number of theoretical<br />\r\nstages in order to reduce the concentration of benzene in raffinate phase upto 0.84 wt% is ________.<br />\r\n(Rounded off to nearest integer)</p>",
      "OPT1": "4",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "znhkQSpRhMmrD25WN956iw==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "5kxMa8YwwyHwJY15nzG3sQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "2",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "Alphanumeric",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu31": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>A batch of water containing residual chlorine from a treating process at a concentration 12 ppm,is to be treated with activated carbon at 25\u00b0C to reduce the chlorine concentration to 0.5 ppm. The carbon consists of 30 mesh granules. Adsorbate diffusional resistance is expected to be small<br />\r\nrelative to that in the liquid. The equilibrium distribution coefficient C*/<em>x</em> = 0.80 [(kg Cl<sub>2</sub>/ m<sup>3\u00a0</sup>liquid)/(kg Cl<sub>2</sub>/kg \u2018C\u2019]. The minimum mass of carbon per unit volume water which can be used is ________ kg/m<sup>3</sup>. (Rounded off 1 decimal places)</p>",
      "OPT1": "18.4",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "FJSw/x9Qjs93mPEXbdv0JA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "5kxMa8YwwyHwJY15nzG3sQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "2",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "Alphanumeric",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu32": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>Which of the following statements is/are false with respect to the dew point of a vapor gas\u00a0mixture?</p>",
      "OPT1": "The dew point is independent of the humidity of the mixture.",
      "OPT2": "The vapor pressure at the dew point is equal to the partial pressure of the vapor.",
      "OPT3": "Dew point is the temperature attained when the mixture is humidified to saturation.",
      "OPT4": "Saturation humidity of the mixture is equal to the saturation humidity at the dew point.",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "fUwGNpwrpUE3GIKhfsyzGA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "fUwGNpwrpUE3GIKhfsyzGA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "5",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu33": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>What are the conditions for equimolar counter diffusion, for species <em>A</em> and <em>B</em>?</p>",
      "OPT1": "Partial pressure gradient of the two diffusing species must be equal but in opposite sign.",
      "OPT2": "The rate of diffusion of these species are equal but in opposite direction.",
      "OPT3": "<em>J<sub>A</sub></em> + <em>J<sub>B</sub></em> = 0",
      "OPT4": "None of the above",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "1tsLNxDzUM4tAESa/gW9mQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "1tsLNxDzUM4tAESa/gW9mQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "5",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "TEST_NAME": "Subjectwise Test-9 Part Syllabus GATE 2026 CH Mass Transfer",
  "TEST_ID_ENCODED": "MTI4ODM5OTQ=",
  "TEST_ID": "MTI4ODM5OTQ="
}